heroin_normal:Alfredo!

alfredo:What is it?

heroin_normal:Do you know anything about the Witch who's kidnapping Humans in Lalaque Forest?

alfredo:……

heroin_normal:…

alfredo:I know better than anyone else.

heroin_smile:Really? Awesome!

heroin_smile:I'll catch that Witch for you! Just tell me where she is!

alfredo:The Witch lures people near the Lalaque Tree.

alfredo:I had been almost within her grasp as well.

heroin_normal:So how did you survive?

alfredo:…

alfredo:The Witch had once been my friend.

alfredo:I think she let me go because she recognized me.

heroin_surprised:…Huh?

heroin_surprsied:How did your friend become a Witch?

alfredo:…

alfredo:It was because I didn't become her friend.

heroin_sigh:What the…you just said she was your friend!

alfredo:But she didn't think of me as one.

heroin_normal:So it was a one-way affection, then.

heroin_normal:…

heroin_sigh:…A crush?

alfredo:…No.

heroin_smile:Hehehe…be honest!

alfredo:She looked so sad.

heroin_normal:?

alfredo:Like me…without friends…getting bullied and picked on…

alfredo:My heart hurt seeing her suffer, so I always took care of her.

heroin_smile:Wow…

alfredo:But she truly despised me.

alfredo:Because…the more I cared, the more the others picked on her, saying 'losers flock together'.

heroin_sigh:Evil kids…

alfredo:I just wanted to be nice to her.

alfredo:But I guess she didn't need a friend like me.

heroin_normal:But why is she doing the Witch thing? Tell her to come back to the village!

alfredo:…

alfredo:She can't come back.

heroin_sigh:Why?

alfredo:She died.

heroin_normal:……

alfredo:Kate took her life, out of loneliness.

alfredo:And even after death, she is lonely…so lonely that she became a spectre that kidnaps people.

alfredo:…For some reason…

alfredo:She rejects me even after becoming a spectre.

alfredo:I think that's why I was safe despite encountering her.

heroin_sigh:You know…you're a sad person, too…

alfredo:It's okay. I'm happy now.

alfredo:I like someone I can behold with love…

alfredo:But I also realized that staying by someone who beholds me with love is also happiness.

heroin_surprised:Whoa…did you get a girlfriend who fell for you?

alfredo:I'm talking about my mother.

heroin_normal:Oh…

alfredo:And I wish Kate would stop kidnapping people from now on.

alfredo:I don't want her to be lonely anymore.

heroin_normal:Let me speak to her first.

heroin_normal:Her name's Kate, right? I'll remember that!!

alfredo:You're a Deity, so…I hope you can do what you say.

alfredo:Help her.

event:0
