4^After restoring all the springs…

4^Pieberry became the new ruler after her mother Elysion.

4^This was not the wish of Elysion or Pieberry.

4^It was the will of the people.

4^Pieberry's reputation grew from Lalaque Village…

4^And even before Pieberry faced the Pope…

4^The yearning for the Age of the Deities had been rising among the masses.

2^#hide

0^heroin:We shall now begin the Prayer Ritual for this month.

0^heroin:Restore the crops of Ellad Village, which have died from flooding…

0^heroin:And permit life once more to Baselle of Ellad Village, who perished while rescuing a child.

0^heroin:I hereby conclude this month's prayers.

0^heroin:……

0^heroin:*sigh*…Wielding the power of the spring is really taxing, mom.

0^eily:Great job…you're adjusting very quickly, dear!

0^eily:The spring is simply a vessel for the magic power - the actual miracle happens through your magic. The spring is merely a…container.

0^heroin:Was the Pope able to wield this much magic power? This is no joke…

0^eily:No…back then, Aramute's magic power remained in the spring. That's why the Pope could wield it.

0^eliy:Actually, it isn't so much that the Pope wielded it…

0^eily:But more akin to the will of Aramute granting the wishes of the Pope, but by bit, I guess!

0^heroin:And since the miracles of the Pope paled in comparison to those of the past Deities…

0^heroin:The Pope kept collecting the Dark Magic Stones, thinking he simply lacked magic power.

0^eliy:Yes. In fact, Aramute manipulated the Pope into revealing his true colors.

0^heroin:And when he was revealed, his power pushed him to kill his own men.

0^heroin:Anyway, I was really surprised! I know you can force the Humans to your will, but you decided to take this path…

0^heroin:Of course, if you did try to force them into submission, they would have struggled all the more to resist you.

0^eliy:You'll understand more as you continue this duty. The reason we had to do what we did…

0^eliy:Humans are weak, so they quickly succumb to evil - and commit heinous acts to become more powerful.

0^eliy:When you see those things, you cannot help but be compelled to help them.

0^heroin:I can't understand everything yet…

0^heroin:But when I view the prayers they bring here, I do feel pity. Such sad stories…

0^blackBird_normal:Master! It's time to inspect the villages!

0^heroin:Huh? Already?

0^eliy:You can do it, Lucia!

0^heroin:*sigh*…This schedule's a killer…
