heroin_smile:Luna!

runa_normal:Hi!

heroin_smile:It's so weird to see you in the village!!

heroin_smile:So you're done living in the Icy Field?

runa_normal:It's cold there. Why would I?

runa_normal:I only lived there to hide from the Warriors!

heroin_normal:Then where did you originally live?

runa_normal:Here.

heroin_surprised:Huh? How did you come to live here?

runa_normal:Hehe…

heroin_sigh:…?

runa_normal:Call me Big Sister.

heroin_sigh:Huh? But why?

runa_normal:You're younger than me…right? You don't know why I lived in this village, because you were born after the War!

heroin_sigh:…I get it.

heroin_sigh:I heard that the Hybrid Deities who lived in the village before the War were expelled…

runa_normal:That's right, dummy.

runa_normal:So that means I'm about ten years older than you! I was kicked out of the village when I was about ten…

runa_normal:And you were probably born around then!

heroin_smile:Pfft! So what?

runa_normal:…Huh?

heroin_smile:A ten-year age difference is nothing!

heroin_smile:Think of the Deities' lifespans! You think being ten years older means you're a Big Sister?!

heroin_smile:You're my friend!

runa_normal:Big Sister!

heroin_smile:Luna! My friend Luna!

runa:…

heroin_smile:Luna! My lovely Luna! Lovely Luna-luna!

runa_normal:…

runa_normal:Shoot. You win.

heroin_normal:By the way…

heroin_normal:Now that I know you live here, I don't have to travel all the way to the Icy Field to meet you!

runa_normal:…Thanks to you.

runa_normal:Thanks, really.

heroin_normal:No, no! I'm the one who's grateful!

heroin_normal:you helped me get to Durok Temple!

runa_normal:Heh. But I didn't think you'd invade the Pope's Castle.

runa_normal:Had I known…I would have ignored you as a crazy Witch.

runa_normal:So, why did you come to this village?

heroin_smile:To see you, of course!

runa_normal:Hmmph…

heroin_smile:Heh.

heroin_normal:I just wanted to visit places.

heroin_normal:I used to be terrified of the area near this village…

heroin_normal:But also curious about a place I never visited!

runa_normal:Ah, I see.

runa_normal:If you're here to see Lord Aramute, head to the temple.

runa_normal:He's really busy these days, so he'll be stuck inside the temple.

runa_normal:Go say hi to him.

heroin_smile:Yeah, okay!

event:0
