event:0

who:Overcome it…Overcome!!

heroin_surprised:Eeek…Why is a Dark Warrior in the Pope's Castle?

heroin_surprised:That Dark Warrior…about half of his energy is still Human.

who:…

who:You also participate in this experiment for power, yes?

who:Dreaming of the status you'll gain when this experiment is successful…

who:But what good is that, if your mind if devoured like so?

cWarrior:…Your Excellency…help me…

pp:Your sacrifice was beautiful, Palace Warrior. Let go of your will now.

pp:Then you shall possess no reason, no emotion, and no more pain.

cWarrior:Aaaaargh…

event:1

pp:*sigh* …Using two or more Dark Magic Stones all result in their minds being devoured.

pp:I require powerful magic power to fully control Aramute's spring…is there no way other than using the Dark Magic Stones…?

pp:…

pp:When the War began…why did the Deities seal away all the springs…

pp:Except Aramute's spring?

pp:And why can I only use the power of Aramute's spring partially?!!

whoVoice:It's a cruel prank by Aramute.

event:2

whoVoice:He did not want to give up the power of the spring. They're all selfish, you know.

pp:What brings you to the lab?

whoVoice:How desperate you've become, Pope.

pp:Just find out the secret of this spring…else, what good are you to me?!

whoVoice:Ha, are you trying to command me? Without me…

pp:Do not think you have the upper hand. I am the one who can use the spring!

pp:The spring rejects you, as you know. Haha…

whoVoice:The only reason you can even use a portion of the spring's power is because I taught you the instructions.

whoVoice:You should be thankful to me.

pp:Ah, but our deal was not about gaining partial power…I want the entire, unleashed power!

whoVoice:Don't be so hasty. I'm almost done uncovering the full unlocking of the spring.

pp:I will not believe it until I learn it.

whoVoice:And I won't teach you, unless you raise my status high enough that even you can't meddle in my affairs.

pp:You are not satisfied with being the Supreme Palace Warrior?

whoVoice:I'm still just your lackey. Did you think I'd make a deal with you so that I can be a pathetic pawn?

pp:…What do you want, then?

whoVoice:The throne of Vavelia.

pp:…!!

whoVoice:At least that will stop you from controlling me after you gain the full power of the spring.

pp:Do you want me to assassinate the king?

whoVoice:No, I know the spring grants wishes, but does not condone murder.

pp:…Then what?

whoVoice:Wage a war.

whoVoice:Use all the Dark Warriors you've amassed so far. Plunge the kingdom into chaos.

whoVoice:The king will not be able to stop them, and all will witness his incompetence. Then you will arrive with the perfect solution.

whoVoice:The people will then trust you completely.

pp:And then you want me to declare you as king?

whoVoice:Yes. Justify it by telling the people that you received a divine revelation about the next king.

pp:…It will not be easy to control the Dark Warriors.

pp:One slight mistake, and I will be devoured by the dark magic…

whoVoice:Of course you will need to risk that much, naturally.

whoVoice:When I am king, I shall fully unlock the power of the spring. You won't need to suffer using the Dark Magic Stones.

pp:……

event:3