event:0

heroin_crisis:What is this place…?

heroin_normal:A temple…? The floor and the walls look similar…

katlin:It's the dungeon under the Pope's Castle.

katlin:It's a remodeled temple, so you're not entirely wrong.

event:1

heroin_normal:Who are you?

katlin:A Witch, here for the same reason as you.

katlin:I'm Michelle.

heroin_normal:Oh…I've heard of you…

heroin_normal:The girl who betrayed Luna?

event:2

katlin:You know Luna? Is she alive?!

heroin_normal:Why so worried, all of a sudden? Didn't you sell her out?

event:3

katlin:…I did.

katlin:And I regret it. Back then…I was so scared…

heroin_normal:Luna's alive. She's pretty strong, so I don't think the Warriors will get her anytime soon.

katlin:Really…? I'm glad she's doing okay…I really am…

katlin:I cried so hard after selling Luna…

katlin:And now I've become a lab rat.

heroin_normal:A lab rat?

katlin:They're studying our powers.

katlin:Thanks to that, I'm still alive…but they might kill me any moment.

heroin_normal:They're studying the power of Deities…? Hmm…

katlin:I think they can't fully control the spring's power. Seems they can't completely channel its potential.

katlin:That's what I heard while being experimented!

heroin_normal:…Ha.

heroin_normal:It will be impossible for them. The springs aren't just pools of power.

katlin:…?

heroin_normal:A spring is a vessel of a god's will. The spring that the Pope possesses, Lord Aramute's spring, is imbued with Lord Aramute's will.

heroin_normal:Therefore, unless Lord Aramute's will permits it, no one can fully control the spring, regardless of the magic power they possess.

event:2

katlin:Oh…that's a new one for me! I just thought the springs were pools of immense magic power, and that the Humans started the War to take it.

heroin_normal:They did, because that's what they believed, but it wasn't true.

heroin_normal:Lord Aimhard told me that he permitted the use of a spring to the Humans, only for a while…

katlin:……Pfah! How can you be so full of hot air in this situation?

katlin:Look, Lord Aimhard died during the War!

katlin:You talk as if you've actually met him!

event:4

heroin_surprised:Eh…? Where's Black Joe?

katlin:Worry about yourself. It will be experiment time soon, and they'll leech your magic power dry.

heroin_normal:Heh, I have Return Magic. I can fly home!

katlin:This is the Papal Dungeon, you idiot! Do you think that will work?

katlin:Clumsy teleportation magic will be blocked instantly!

heroin_oing:…Oh…then what should I do…?

katlin:Full of hot air…idiot…

event:5

crown:You're now awake. It's been awhile.

heroin_surprised:Crown!! How did you get here…?

crown_normal:I'm the Supreme Palace Warrior. I can go wherever I please within the Pope's Castle.

event:6

heroin_smile:It's open! I'm out of this horrible, wet, dark place!

katlin:Wha…? What happened?

heroin_normal:Crown! Free that girl in the next cell!

crown_normal:I won't. You can't trust the Hybrid Deities.

heroin_sad:Oh…you said that the Hybrids plotted with the Humans…

heroin_normal:But she doesn't seem evil…

katlin:…Well? What are you talking about, instead of freeing me?

crown_normal:Most guards have been dispatched elsewhere.

crown_normal:Also, Aramute's spring rests on top of this prison.

heroin_crisis:…!!!

crown_normal:The Pope always stays there, so you should avoid it.

heroin_crisis:Lord Aramute's spring is just above the prison? I have to go there now!

heroin_crisis:The reason mom is sealed inside a spring…and why I've been branded a Witch and hunted all my life…it's all because of the Pope!

crown_normal:The choice is yours. But so is the risk for putting your life in danger.

crown_normal:If you want to escape, go to the last large prison cell. A Warp Gate that leads to other temples lies there.

crown_normal:I wish you luck.

event:7

heroin_normal:……

katlin:Owww!! No one's freeing me, after all!!

heroin_normal:I'll get you out. Just be patient.

katlin:…I doubt it. Why would you?

katlin:Bah, just run away. There's no guarantee you'll live long even if you flee…!

heroin_normal:(First, I have to find my staff and Black Joe…I can sense Black Joe's energy strongly from somewhere…)

event:8