heroin_normal:We’re near the spring, so it's going to be a rough battle, right?

blackBird_normal:Probably. And Light Spirits are tough…

event:0

lightingbell:Strange…

heroin_smile:Ha. Your health is recovering quicker than usual, is it?

lightingbell:…?!

heroin_smile:That's all thanks to me! And look behind you! Here it comes!

event:1

lightingbell:…! Lord Aimhard!!

aimhard:It has been awhile, Lighting Bell.

event:2

lightingbell:But…how…?

aimhard:I told you, Lighting Bell.

aimhard:Someone will come to restore this spring…

event:3

lion:Greetings, Lord Aimhard.

aimhard:Ah…Aslan! Why are you here? You should be guarding Arua!

lion:This young Deity has awoken my master. Lord Arua received help from this one.

aimhard:Oho…still a cute girl, I see! I thought you would be taller by now…

heroin_smile:I'm Pieberry! Wait, what do you mean by 'still'? …Have we met before?

aimhard:Ha…not important. Pieberry, you say? I shall call you Little Lady for now!

heroin_smile:Hehe, whatever suits you.

lightingbell:Aslan, I apologize for my suspicions.

heroin_normal:I told you!

lion:I did not believe this Deity at first, either. I thought she was only a husk.

aimhard:Haha…let me reward you for a job well done!

event:4

blackBird_normal:He's finally awake. Would have been nice if he did so before we fought.

heroin_smile:Hello!

aimhard:Oho…still a cute girl, I see! I thought you would be taller by now…

heroin_smile:I'm Pieberry! Wait, what do you mean by 'still'? …Have we met before?

aimhard:Ha…not important. Pieberry, you say? I shall call you Little Lady for now!

heroin_smile:Hehe, whatever suits you.

lightingbell:Aslan, I apologize for my suspicions.

heroin_normal:I told you!

lion:I did not believe this Deity at first, either. I thought she was only a husk.

aimhard:Haha…let me reward you for a job well done!

event:5

heroin_surprised:Wow! My body feels sturdier!

aimhard:I have placed my blessing on you. It will be with you always from now on.

heroin_smile:Thank you!! You're so amazing, Lord Aimhard!

aimhard:Haha, then I shall ask a favor of you, Little Deity Lady!

aimhard:Will you awaken the sleeping Deities of the other springs?

heroin_smile:Fine with me! But what happens when all the springs are restored?

aimhard:This is the short version, but…

aimhard:We will be able to protect the Humans once more.

heroin_surprised:What?! Protect the…Humans?

aimhard:By your looks, the Humans must be causing you pain…much pain. I am sorry that we placed such a burden on you.

aimhard:In fact, we sealed all the springs but one, and gave it away to the Humans on purpose.

heroin_surprised:…On purpose…?

heroin_angry:I don't understand!

aimhard:You will understand more when you find other springs.

heroin_sad:I don't want to understand, really…

heroin_normal:Of course, I do have a reason to find the springs. To become stronger!

aimhard:You don't need to understand for now. You will, in the end.

aimhard:You have the most amazing blessing other than my own, so you will walk the right path.

heroin_normal:(…? Is he talking about the blessing of Lord Arua?)

aimhard:Then I shall end my words here. The Humans will keep causing you pain, but I wish you luck!

heroin_smile:Okay, Lord Aimhard!

aimhard:Oh! And take Lighting Bell with you. She will be quite useful.

lightingbell:But…Master?! I wish to guard your site!

aimhard:Now that my mind is restored, I am more than safe with my magic power. Go help the Little Lady.

lightingbell:…But!

blackBird_normal:Welcome to the club.

heroin_smile:Thank you!!

lightingbell:Gah.

event:6
