aimhard:Ah, Little One!

heroin_smile:Hello, Lord Aimhard!

aimhard:You've become even fairer since last time! And you've grown taller!

heroin_shy:Hehe…really?

heroin_smile:Thank you for the compliment!

aimhard:I'm glad you came by, as I had been a bit bored!

heroin_normal:Oh…my mom says she's always busy…but Lord Aimhard, you're not…?

aimhard:Aramute is the busiest, trying to rebuild all that were destroyed…

aimhard:The next will be Elysion, who oversees life.

aimhard:Or would that be Arua, who manages the weather?

aimhard:I'm the god who seals dangerous zones.

aimhard:So I really do not have much to do, despite my revival!

heroin_oing:Haha…so that's why you're so free…

heroin_normal:Even more than Lord Durok??

aimhard:He is simply slightly busy for the moment!

aimhard:His work will be over once he transports some collapsed boulders near Aramute Village.

aimhard:I did the lion's share of work for eons! The sheer number of barriers I erected, for example…!

aimhard:And I have to constantly inject my magic power into the barriers to maintain them!

aimhard:It may look easy, but it is no walk in the park, I tell you!

aimhard:Now, Durok - he has the easiest job!

heroin_oing:Haha…no need to get so riled up…

aimhard:Ah…

aimhard:My apologies. I do not relish losing to that fellow.

aimhard:Always so aloof, with an expression that beams with pride!

heroin_sigh:Haha…or maybe it's because you're upset that Lord Durok doesn't respond to your jokes, Lord Aimhard?

aimhard:……

aimhard:No. Definitely not.

aimhard:I am a god. Lord Aimhard!

aimhard:Do you believe that I am so petty?

heroin_smile:Sure, okay, then.

aimhard:No…Little One…I speak the truth…Truly…Ohh…

heroin_smile:Okay, then.

aimhard:Bah…fine.

aimhard:I shall admit it with grace. I am slightly upset about Durok!

aimhard:But this is all because I wish to befriend him!

aimhard:Aramute is always busy. Arua is boring. Elysion is too modest.

aimhard:But Durok always criticizes me.

aimhard:That delights me. A conversation can actually persist when it is initiated with him.

aimhard:Of course, we always end up arguing…heh.

heroin_smile:Haha…now I see.

heroin_smile:You're really honest, Lord Aimhard!

aimhard:Where is the need for a god to be modest and arcane?

heroin_smile:I know! And I think that's what makes you so charming, Lord Aimhard!

aimhard:Ha…! So true, indeed!

heroin_smile:Haha, sure, okay then.

event:0
