heroin_crisis:*gasp gasp* …

blackBird_normal:Master, if you must kill him now! Else he'll come after you again!

heroin_smile:Hmm…but…he's the best-looking Warrior I've met!

blackBird_normal:This isn't the time to admire looks!!!

heroin_smile:I'm Pieberry! Humans call me the Black Witch!

heroin_smile:You! Promise me you'll never attack again, and I'll let you live!

justice_normal:I am called Justice. And as per my namesake, I live for righteousness and do not beg for mercy to evil… 

heroin_sigh:I said I'll let you live…but you don't want that? That's messed up…

justice_normal:Just kill me!

heroin_sigh:*sigh* …Why do I never get recognized for my mercy…?

event:0

heroin_angry:Heh! Just know that you're the one to blame here!

event:1

justice_normal:Uggh………

event:2 

heroin_normal:Still, I'll let you live. I've never killed anyone, see!

justice_normal:…!

heroin_normal:I'm not addicted to killing like you people.

justice_normal:Just kill me, I said!

heroin_smile:I'm gonna spare you, I said!

justice_normal:Uggh…such shame…I won't forget this…ever…!

heroin_normal:Take care of your body. You're hurt badly.

justice_normal:Uggh!!

event:3

blackBird_normal:He fainted. He won't be able to move for a while.

event:4

heroin_normal:Black Joe…

blackBird_normal:Yes, Master.

heroin_sad:Why do the Humans hate me so? I've never done anything particularly bad…

blackBird_normal:…

blackBird_normal:Actually, Witches are the descendants of the Deities. And the Deities once ruled over Humans.

heroin_normal:…I'm a Deity?

blackBird_normal:The Deities of the past - the Witches of the present - are threats to the Humans.

blackBird_normal:The Humans are hunting Witches for the fear that the Deities might rule them again.

heroin_normal:…But I'm not interested in Humans! Why would I rule them…?

blackBird_normal:Not all Witches are like you, and so you're also a target of the Witch Hunt.

heroin_surprised:There are other Witches besides me?

blackBird_normal:Not many, but yes.

heroin_normal:…!

blackBird_normal:Sometimes Witches are born from Humans. But then they're eliminated immediately for their looks…

blackBird_normal:Or abandoned in forests.

heroin_normal:…

blackBird_normal:You were probably one of the lucky ones who were abandoned, Master.

heroin_sad:……

blackBird_normal:…Master…?

heroin_sad:……

blackBird_normal:Master…are you crying?

heroin_normal:…Shut up.

heroin_normal:…I was always alone, anyway. That I was an abandoned baby means nothing.

blackBird_normal:Be strong, Master.

event:5