heroin_crisis:*gasp gasp* …

blackBird_normal:Careful. It's still not fully defeated! It's too close to the spring!

heroin_crisis:!!

event:0

none-5:…

heroin_crisis:It's too strong, and not even out of breath! This is too much!

blackBird_normal:…! Wait, its vicious aura is gone!

heroin_normal:??

none-5:My wounds have healed, again…?

heroin_oing:Huh? It looks surprised, too!

blackBird_normal:Maybe it's the first time it has been wounded that much.

event:1

none-5:The spring…is being restored.

event:2

none-5:You have realized my master's will once again.

heroin_normal:Aha, so it was the spring that was calling me ever since we came to this island.

none-5:You shall be tested. Stand before the spring.

blackBird_normal:Master, I can sense elevated Deity energy! Don't approach it!

heroin_normal:Be quiet. I've felt someone calling me for a while.

blackBird_normal:We don't know how a Deity's spring will react to a Witch's unclean energy! It's too dangerous!

heroin_normal:Shut up.

event:3

none-1:To the one who hears my voice…I knew you would come, sooner or later.

heroin_normal:I don't know your voice, but you seem familiar.

arua:My name is Arua. The lord of this spring.

heroin_smile:Arua? That's a nice name! I'm Pieberry!

arua:Let me ask you this. What is your creed?

heroin_normal:What the…? I don't have a creed. I just have to become stronger, so I can survive!

arua:Haha…I see.

arua:I shall look forward to seeing what creed and will you will uphold in the future.

arua:And since you have awoken me, I shall give you a gift.

event:4

heroin_surprised:Wow…! My body is overflowing with power…! This is so awesome!

heroin_smile:Thank you, Lord Arua! Mind if I visit now and then?

arua:As I have given you my magic power, I must now sleep once more.

heroin_surprised:Eh…? But you just woke up…! Then why did you give me your magic power?

arua:The answer lies in the other temple springs.

heroin_surprised:There are more springs? Will they also give me power, like this one?!

arua:Of course. With your current power, you will be able to face Aimhard's Guardian Beast.

heroin_smile:Wow! Then I better get going!

arua:There are five springs, including mine.

arua:Among them, only Aramute's spring, which has been seized by the Humans, has not been sealed. The rest are sealed, as mine was.

arua:If the seal lasts for too long, the springs will be closed forever.

heroin_normal:Oh…so I have to hurry? How long do I have left?

arua:In ^rDays days, all the springs will be closed. Even the Aramute Spring, which is currently opened.

heroin_surprised:^rDays days left? Then it's going to be soon…So what happens if I restore all the springs?

arua:As I have said, search for the answer at the next spring.

heroin_sigh:Wish you could just tell me…now I'm curious…

arua:Aimhard's temple lies to the north. It is also the home of Aslan, so you should take him with you.

heroin_normal:Take him with me?

none-5:My master has acknowledged you.

none-5:Now my master's will has been marked upon you. Thus, you are also my master.

event:5

heroin_smile:Wow! You're really going to be my pet?!

blackBird_normal:Stupid…why volunteer for torment?

heroin_smile:Okay, then! You're my minion, too!

heroin_normal:Yay!! But first…

event:6

none-5:Miniaturization?

heroin_smile:Ooh, you're so cute now!!

none-5:…

heroin_smile:It's difficult to take you when you're so big! Now you're small enough to raise in my house!

heroin_normal:Wow…I like this spring! It gave me a pet and more powers!

blackBird_normal:Let's go home, Master. We've battled for so long.

heroin_smile:Yeah. I've got a cute lion today, so I'm satisfied! Let's return!

heroin_smle:Thank you, Lord Arua!

arua:…

heroin_normal:(He's gone back to sleep…)

event:7