event:-1

heroin_normal:(…?! The spring's power was granted to me!)

heroin_sigh:(He could have given it to me earlier…why give it after everything is over…?)

pp:Gaah…Uuurrrgh…………!!

heroin_normal:Divine power? Ha! Overrated, I think…

warriors:Protect the Pope!!

event:0

heroin_normal:You weakling Warriors are no match for me!

warriors:…Your Excellency…I am sorry…

pp:Ughh…useless fools……

heroin_normal:This is the end for you.

event:1

pp:Wait…spare me…

heroin_smile:Oh? Is the divine Pope begging for his life to a filthy Witch?

pp:I have so much to do…I must pray for the dying lands…and go on pilgrimages…

heroin_normal:Others can do that in your stead.

pp:Ah……

pp:Then you leave me no choice. I did not want to do this…

event:2

warriors:What?! Why did the Pope release the Dark Warriors from their prison…?!!

pp:Thankfully, they will compensate for your incompetence.

pp:They are also your old companions who have already sacrificed themselves for the greater good…

warriors:What…?

pp:These are Warriors who have volunteered to be experimented with Dark Magic Stone implants. I promised them greater status should they be successful. 

pp:Of course, they failed, and now have become mindless Dark Warriors…

pp:But they are now far more brave and powerful.

heroin_normal:You're confessing to everything, idiot! I thought the Humans weren't supposed to know all of that?

pp:Hehehe…no matter, since I will kill them all.

warriors:Your Excellency…!!

event:3

justice_normal:A commotion in the Main Hall…

justice_normal:The Black Witch…and Dark Warriors!!

warriors:Sir Justice!! You see…

event:4

pp:I command thee, Dark Warriors.

justice_normal:!!

pp:Slay all those here, including the Witch!

warriors:Your Excellency…!!

event:5

justice_normal:Your Excellency!! What the hell is this?!!

pp:'What the hell'? Is that how a Palace Warrior addresses his Pope?

justice_normal:That's not the issue here!

pp:Justice, you are young and competent. And extremely righteous.

pp:…Which is your main problem. You are too by-the-book to accept anything other than the straight path.

pp:It is a shame that you had to witness this. I truly regret what I am about to do.

justice_normal:Your Excellency!!

pp:Destroy them.

event:6

justice_normal:Ack…!

event:7

heroin_normal:Justice! You owe me one!

event:8

pp:But how…even the Dark Warriors…?

heroin_normal:You used the Dark Magic Stone, right? I've faced this creepy energy enough times to recognize it.

heroin_normal:You forbade the Humans from using the stones so that you could collect them, right? Divine power? What a joke!!

pp:I must control the spring fully, if I am to spread more miracles to the people…

pp:But that requires great magic power…

pp:And the Dark Magic Stones can provide such incredible power…

pp:Behold…the full channeling of the dark magic!!

pp:…What?

pp:WHAT??…

event:9

pp:Aaaaarggh!!!!

heroin_normal:He's channeled too much dark magic.

heroin_sigh:I thought he wanted to live, yet…

event:10

pp:Hear me…O spring! Hear my wish!!

pp:Save me!! Gaaah!!!

event:11

pp:Yes…YES!! Purify me!! Hurry!!!!

event:12

heroin_smile:Oh, Crown!

justice_normal:Sir Crown!

pp:What…What?

event:13

pp:…………Gaaaaaah!!

heroin_normal:…So…

justice_normal:Was that the power of the spring…?

heroin_normal:It cleansed the entire area, along with the Dark Warriors…?

crown_normal:Did you all see that?

heroin_smile:I bet they did!

event:14

crown_normal:The Black Witch killed the Pope with an evil curse. We shall execute her right now.

heroin_surprised:…!! What?

warriors:Sir Crown, but…

crown_normal:All who object will be considered an ally of the Witch, and killed on the spot.

heroin_crisis:Crown…!!

crown_normal:Justice! You will carry it out. The others seem to have lost the will to fight.

justice_normal:Sir Crown, there seems to be a misunderstanding. The Witch…

crown_normal:I will do it, if you're unwilling.

heroin_crisis:What…what's going on?!!

event:15