event:0

heroin_crisis:*gasp gasp* ……

event:1

heroin_crisis:…!!!

crown_normal:…Ha.

heroin_crisis:Uggh…! He's barely hurt, if at all…!

crown_normal:And this was your full might?

heroin_crisis:My magic power…I can't…

event:2

heroin_angry:Black Joe! Come back right now!

event:3

heroin_surprised:Black Joe…!!

blackBird_normal:Ma…Master…

heroin_angry:Aaaaaah…!!

event:4

crown_normal:That was entertaining…but enough of this.

heroin_crisis:Gah…!

event:5

heroin_crisis:*groan*…… … .

crown_normal:I'd hoped for some entertainment, but you are nothing but a child.

heroin_sad:(…Too strong…)

heroin_sad:(Was I fated to be killed by a Warrior…?) 

blackBird:Grrrrrr…

event:6

crown_opened:…Bah…my helmet…

heroin_surprised:…Black Joe…?

event:7

crown_opened:…Elysion's Guardian Beast, is it? I was not expecting a disguise.

event:8

heroin_surprised:…Deity?

crown_opened:You must be a Pureblood Deity, since you command a Guardian Beast.

heroin_crisis:What…are you talking about?

event:9

crown_opened:It's sealed, but seems to awaken in response to threats against its master.

crown_opened:It will reawaken if I attack you once again.

heroin_crisis:……

crown_opened:I apologize for being slightly hard-handed. I am Crown, also a Deity.

heroin_angry:Slightly hard-handed? We…we almost died! And why did you attack me, if you knew I was a Deity?

crown_opened:I presumed that you were a Fallen Deity who came lusting for the temple spring.

heroin_crisis:A Fallen Deity? What's that?

crown_opened:There are Deities who are born from Humans. Hybrids, they are called.

crown_opened:They were to serve the Pureblood Deities.

crown_opened:But they envied us, the Pureblood Deities, and schemed with the Humans to wage war upon us…to seize the springs we guarded.

heroin_surprised:Oh…

heroin_normal:Then what are you doing here?

crown_opened:I am a Supreme Palace Warrior. I received news of a Witch appearing in Aimhard Temple, and was investigating the temples.

heroin_normal:(Justice…)

heroin_crisis:Huh…?? But why are you a Warrior?!

crown_opened:I plan to reclaim the springs lost to Humans, and reinstating the Age of Deities.

crown_opened:So I serve as a Warrior under the Pope incognito, for the time being.

crown_opened:It is my goal to retake Aramute Temple from the Pope.

heroin_surprised:Whoa…!

crown_opened:So, what brings you to this temple?

heroin_smile:Oh…I was just visiting! I'm really curious, see? I'm going to go see all the other temples, too!

heroin_smile:그Crown, was it? I'm Pieberry! Also known as the Black Witch among Humans!

crown_opened:The Black Witch…yes, I have heard of you.

crown_opened:We will surely meet again. Be well.

event:10

blackBird_normal:*cough cough*…

event:11

heroin_normal:Feeling better?

blackBird_normal:Gah…the Warrior! Are you alright, Master?!

heroin_normal:Never thought you'd worry about me so much! You even pushed me into the sea, remember?

blackBird_normal:We were really on the brink of death this time!!

heroin_normal:So, why don't you reveal your true self? You! You're a Guardian Beast, right?

blackBird_normal:…??

heroin_normal:Hey, don't you remember? You turned super big!

blackBird_normal:Nope. I think you were hit on the head too many times by that Warrior…

heroin_normal:…

heroin_sigh:Can't rule that out, I guess…Whatever. Anyway, thanks…for saving me…

blackBird_normal:Hehe, my sacrifices are finally being recognized.

blackBird_normal:The spring is just ahead. Don't worry, there won't be any Guardian Beasts!

heroin_normal:…

event:12