event:0

heroin_normal:You're safe now!

fishMan:Whew…thank you for saving me.

heroin_normal:Huh…you're not scared of seeing me?

fishMan:Scared of a Deity? Nonsense. There's so much I've received from Lord Arua…

heroin_smile:Oh? So you're not going to call me a Witch?

fishMan:A Witch? Never!

fishMan:I know we Humans started the War to seize the power of the springs.

heroin_normal:…Can you tell me about the War in detail?

fishMan:Ah…you must be a Deity born after the War, as you are unfamiliar with it.

fishMan:All the nearby villagers worked as fishermen without any accidents, thanks to Lord Arua.

fishMan:The storms blow hard near the island village, but Lord Arua always calmed the winds with the miracle of his spring.

fishMan:He asked for nothing, and only gave.

fishMan:To be truthful, he did not need the fish we caught for him. He's a god…what would he need from us?

fishMan:But after the war, only Lord Aramute's spring remained. The rest were sealed.

fishMan:And not all the villages can receive miracles from the single spring managed by the Papacy.

fishMan:And naturally, no one in our secluded village can create miracles.

heroin_normal:Hmm…why was only Lord Aramute's spring not sealed?

fishMan:I do not know. However…

fishMan:The Deities were never so weak to be overcome by Humans. They probably knew that the Humans would wage war.

fishMan:I do not think it is coincidence that all but a single spring was sealed.

heroin_normal:I see…

heroin_smile:Don't worry!

fishMan:…?

heroin_smile:I'll restore all the springs! I'll stop the storms from harassing you!

fishMan:Oh, how kind of you to say that…

fishMan:Please. Just be safe. I heard there are few Deities left since the Witch Hunts of the Warriors began.

fishMan:We will always be thankful for what your kind has done for us.

heroin_normal:I'll choose my path.

heroin_normal:You stay safe until then, too!

fishMan:My prayers to you. The Deities of the past must have prepared a path for you.

event:1
