crown:Impossible…how could you have grown so powerful, so quickly?

heroin_normal:I now have the power of my mom and the other gods with me!

blackBird_normal:Do you remember the prophecy of the gods? Your master probably told you.

crown_normal:…Damn the prophecy…

event:0

aramute:Do what you wish to do. The time is right.

jude:What do you mean?

aramute:Your scheme will succeed.

aramute:However, it will ultimately fail due to a girl who shall be prepared.

aramute:Remember that all of this was permitted by us.

event:1

crown:No…no. It was just the ramblings of a deluded old fool…

crown:Nonsense…this small girl will put an end to all my plans…?

heroin_sad:Why did you let me go at the prison, then attack me all of a sudden…? We're both Deities…

crown:Hahaha…!! We're 'both' Deities?

crown:I'm a Hybrid. A slave meant to serve you Deities!

heroin_surprised:You…!!

crown:Did you think it was coincidence that you were brought here?

crown:You were brought here to slay the Pope.

crown:It wouldn't do for a Supreme Palace Warrior like me to be seen killing the Pope, you see.

crown:I knew that once I freed you from prison, you would come here.

heroin_crisis:…But…why do you want to kill me?!

crown:A Warrior who kills a Witch gains the confidence of the people.

crown:If that Witch is also a Pope-killer, then…

heroin_crisis:So you used me…? To gain the trust of Humans?!

crown:To establish my own kingdom. The Pope was also a mere tool for my plan…

crown:Recently, the Pope had been growing quite bold…even though I was the one who taught him how to use the spring.

blackBird_normal:Master, that's Jude. The cause of all wars…

heroin_normal:What?!

blackBird_normal:His real name is Jude. He was a Guardian Beast of Lord Aramute.

blackBird_normal:He plotted with the Humans to wage the War and seize the springs.

blackBird_normal:I couldn't recognize his humanoid form before…but when he channeled his power during the last battle, I finally could.

crown:I will fight you in my true form, then…

crown:Your prophecy won't come true… Despair in the face of absolute power…!!

event:2

blackBird_normal:Now he shows his true form. But that's not all!

blackBird_normal:His power is growing…and his size will increase as well!!

heroin_crisis:The building is about to collapse…! Let's move!

event:3

warriors:What's going on?! The Pope, and now Sir Crown…!!

justice_normal:Hurry up and get out!!

justice_normal:Carry the wounded men near you, and run towards the exit!!

event:4

blackBird_normal:Master! Wait!!

blackBird_normal:You now have all the magic power of the springs. You have to find Lord Aramute's room!

heroin_crisis:Why?! Shouldn't we be leaving now?!

blackBird_normal:When Jude fully turns back to his real form, even you can't stop him.

blackBird_normal:We must receive help from the gods!

blackBird_normal:There's a Control Crystal in Lord Aramute's room that supervises all the springs!

blackBird_normal:I'll explain the details when we get there! We have to find Lord Aramute's room now!

event:5