event:0

heroin_normal:…Oh…

blackBird_normal:…

heroin_normal:This feeling…this warmth I felt when sleeping under the tree…

wormVoice:Welcome, dear…!

heroin_normal:Huh…oh!

heroin_smile:I…I know your voice! I heard it in my dreams!

wormVoice:Haha…really?

wormVoice:You probably heard it outside of your dream, too.

heroin_normal:What…?

event:1

wormVoice:I missed you, Lucia.

heroin_smile:Hehe…who's Lucia? I'm Pieberry!

wormVoice:Pieberry? Who gave you that name?

heroin_smile:I gave it to myself! Because I love pie and berries SO MUCH!

wormVoice:…Oh…

heroin_normal:…?

heroin_normal:…Hello?

wormVoice:…

heroin_smile:Why are you so quiet? Were you disappointed by my name?

event:2

blackBird_normal:No!! If you materialize, your magic power will drain, Master…!

heroin_normal:…Master?

event:3

heroin_normal:…?

event:4

heroin_smile:……

heroin_smile:…You're warm.

heroin_smile:Much more than in my dream…

event:5

wormVoice:I'm sorry I couldn't be with you till the end, Lucia…

heroin_smile:Oh…I'm not Lucia. I'm Pieberry…I told you…

event:6

heroin_sad:Hey…are you crying?

blackBird_normal:…

blackBird_normal:Lady Elysion is your mother.

event:7

heroin_normal:…??

heroin_normal:What do you mean…? You said I was abandoned by the village!

blackBird_normal:I lied to you, so that you would stay away from the Humans.

blackBird_normal:If you found out about your secret of your birth and the War started by the Humans, you might have sought revenge…

blackBird_normal:That's why I didn't want to take you to the temples.

event:8

eliy:Ark took you into the forest, during the War.

eliy:And…I asked Balt the Forest Spirit for a favor. To guard my daughter against all Humans…

eliy:And to stop her if she ever tried to approach the Human village before she became powerful…

heroin_surprised:……

eliy:But I knew you would come someday…

eliy:I'm so glad you came to me…Thank you…

heroin_sad:…

heroin_sad:Are you…really my mom?

event:9

eliy:Lucia…I…your mother…

eliy:Loves you so very, very much…!

event:10

heroin_sad:Waah…Waaah……this is my first time ever…

heroin_sad:First time someone held me…told me they loved me…and first time seeing my mom…

eliy:I'm so sorry…so sorry…!

heroin_sad:I have…so much to ask…

heroin_sad:But right now…

heroin_sad:I just want to stay this way…

heroin_sad:I love this moment…so much…!

event:11

heroin_surprised:…M…mom?

heroin_surprised:Are you okay?

event:12

heroin_surprised:Black Joe! What's happening? Why is mom…?

blackBird_normal:She can't materialize herself for long…

eliy:Lucia, I'm okay.

eliy:I will have to sleep again…

eliy:But I really wanted to hold you once more.

heroin_surprised:Oh…but…!

eliy:Let me put this new robe on you, before I go.

eliy:I've imbued all my magic power into it, so it will protect you from danger!

heroin_surprised:…Don't go!

eliy:I love you…let's meet again…!

event:13

blackBird_normal:I wanted to keep it a secret till the end…and I'm not sure if I made the right call to bring you here.

blackBird_normal:I'm sorry for lying to you. I dropped you into the ocean because to stop you from going to the temple…

event:14

heroin_normal:Hey.

blackBird_normal:*gasp* The Master's form, it's…!

blackBird_normal:(Did she react to Lady Eysion's magic power…? I've never seen anything like this…)

blackBird_normal:Y-yes?

heroin_normal:How do I fully restore the springs?

blackBird_normal:You must unite the five springs into one.

heroin_normal:Into a single spring? But they're all separated by distance!

blackBird_normal:I know. It won't be possible.

heroin_normal:You're hiding something more. I can tell when you're lying now!

blackBird_normal:*gulp*

heroin_angry:Spit it out!! I want to see my mom again!!!

blackBird_normal:…

blackBird_normal:Oh…alright.

blackBird_normal:You have the magic powers of Lord Arua, Lord Aimhard, and your mother, Lady Elysion coursing inside you.

blackBird_normal:If you liberate the remaining springs…

blackBird_normal:All the magic power of the springs will unite in the final spring.

heroin_normal:Ha…so I only have two more to go? It won't take long, then!

blackBird_normal:The problem lies with the Aramute Temple. The Humans are using it as the Pope's Castle.

heroin_normal:Then what about the other temple Crown mentioned? Let's go there first.

blackBird_normal:It's north of the Boar Plains. It's difficult to reach due to the frigid temperature.

heroin_normal:No matter. Let's head there now!!

blackBird_normal:(…Oh…I do hope I made the right choice…)

blackBird_normal:(…And…Lady Elysion forgot to dispel my Ugly Bird spell…!!)

blackBird_normal:(…Gaaah! I forgot to ask her, because I became so used to this form!!)

blackBird_normal:…

blackBird_normal:Master! You can do it!! Let's go find that temple! Mwahahaha!!

heroin_normal:…What? Why are you so excited after being so gloomy?

event:15