0/My first successful offense magic fusion! I should try it on the monsters in the Pudding Cave to the east!
1/Maybe I should get a pet by using Mind Control magic? A boar seems to be wandering near my house…!
2/Met a Warrior named Alfredo - he was really weak. Still, I think he keeps following me. I felt a presence in the Pudding Cave, too…or was I imagining it?
3/The swamp downward from my house was too filthy to cross, but maybe I can do it on the back of a boar?
4/I adopted an ugly black bird as my pet. He's called Black Joe! But what good is an ugly, black bird to me…?
5/Black Joe pushed me into the sea…he will pay for this!
6/I caught Black Joe again, by chance! I'll torment him for eternity…! Anyway, I wonder what lies on the South Island?
7/I met a huge lion. He's a Guardian Beast that lost his master, which is a bit sad…
8/I found a mysterious spring in the South Island Temple! Suddenly, Lord Arua, the spring's ruler, spoke to me, gave me powers, then went to sleep. He said there are five springs, all sealed except one, and if the seals last too long they will become permanent…The next temple with a spring is said to be to the north!
9/I met a handsome Warrior. His name was Justice, I think…? But he hated me a lot. Even other Warriors don't talk to me like that…
10/Lord Aimhard also gave me power! Yay…!! But why should I search for the next spring to help the Humans? I don't understand!
11/I had a nightmare…I was captured by a large bird…and what Black Joe told me also haunts my mind. I was abandoned? Does that mean I was born in a Human village? Will my parents be there if I visited the place…? The closest village is Lalaque Village to the east…
12/Met Justice again. He truly hates me! No, EVERYONE hates me!!
13/Black Joe, who hasn’t been supportive of me opening the temple gates, has for some reason told me the location of a temple. A path to a temple lies inside the Golem Cave? I've never seen it…! I'm glad that he helped me to cheer me up from my gloom. I like the power that the springs give me, but I'm also lonely…
14/I defeated a really large Golem. A Dark Golem? Black Joe says it was created with Dark Magic Stone by Humans to wage war, but was abandoned after the war because it couldn't be controlled.
15/I had a wonderful dream. I was in the embrace of someone I didn't know…
16/I met the Supreme Palace Warrior Crown. He was extremely powerful…and a Deity like me! He said he was undercover as a Palace Warrior in order to reclaim the spring the Pope stole from us.
17/I met my mom for the first time in my life. I was held tightly by her…and was told that she loved me…for the first time ever.
18/I have to gather all the magic power of the springs, if I want to meet mom again? The next temple is Durok Temple! Heading out to the northern Icy Field!
19/Huh? Another Witch, like me! Hello, Luna! And she's a Deity who was born in the village? Her mother's a Human, she said.
20/Durok Temple lies beyond the glacier…but Black Joe can't fly over it! Luna told me that there is a path through the Ice Cave near the entrance to the Icy Field! And I should follow the light to find the way inside the Ice Cave!
21/Temar…! That was the first Dragon I ever saw. And he'll help me in battle, when I call? Awesome!!
22/Lord Durok's not very talkative. He just gave me his magic power and went to sleep.
23/There was a Palace Warrior at the Durok Temple entrance…and then soon after, another Warrior ambushed me…did they know that I was coming? I've been captured…
24/Crown unlocked the prison door for me! First, I have to find my staff and Black Joe…! I can sense Black Joe's energy strongly around me! But…was his energy always this powerful?
25/Black Joe attacked me when his seal was broken. I beat him up and restored his form, but I'll be sure to beat him up again when we get home.
26/Lord Aramute's spring was said to be on top of the prison. When I gather the last spring's magic power, I'll be able to meet mom!
27/Crown was a traitor to the Deities! He kidnapped me to kill the Pope?! And then he was going to kill me…bastard!
28/The building's about to collapse! I have to find Lord Aramute's room quickly!
29/Today, I'll be fusing Flame Magic! I just need to get two Superdry Leaves from under the trees, and Blue Sand from the beach!
30/Ralph is an aloof merchant who only cares for profit. So he's not very charming, but it also means he's safe to deal with! Ralph never sells me out to the Warriors. Because I can get items Ralph wants!
31/[Ralph's Request] Ralph wants me to get a King Pudding. The Pudding Cave is east of my house!
32/[Ralph's Request] Ralph now wants me to fetch a Magic Slab! The Golem who has the Magic Slab will be east to find, since it's always at the end of the Golem Cave on the hill back of my house!
33/[Ralph's Request] South Island still has Bigcrabs, right? I wonder how much Ralph will pay this time?
34/[Ralph's Request] Lavastone must be hard to find, since he's willing to pay so much! It's deep inside the Golem Cave…
35/[Ralph's Request] How can he casually ask me to get material for crafting Warrior blades that may be used to kill me…? The Black Lion is said to live up north.
36/[Ralph's Request] Now the Pope ordered a Dark Magic Stone? But it contains magic power too strong for Humans…anyway, Dark Warriors should have Dark Magic Stones!
37/[Ralph's Request] An Old Yetiman's heart is said to be completely frozen. I'm supposed to acquire it.
38/[Ralph's Request] Why do Humans create something they cannot wield, then throw it away? Anyway, the Lavastein Golem should be near the Lava Golem, right?
39/[Ralph's Request] Dragons are too strong, even for a party of Warriors…*sigh*…so annoying. The Zirconia Dragon's Egg in the Dragon Valley, is it?
40/[Ralph's Request] He wants me to hunt down a legendary Dragon that no one has ever defeated…hahaha…I think the Lightning Dragon lives in Dragon Valley.
41/[Ralph's Request Completed] The King Pudding request has been completed! Ralph left for the village to trade. He'll come back in a couple of days.
42/[Ralph's Request Completed] Magic Slab request complete!
43/[Ralph's Request Completed] Bigcrab request complete!
44/[Ralph's Request Completed] Lavastone request complete! But can the Humans even use this magically powerful stone? Who orders these things?
45/[Ralph's Request Completed] Black Lion Teeth request complete!
46/[Ralph's Request Completed] Dark Magic Stone request complete! That Pope, collecting this in secret while banning it publicly…
47/[Ralph's Request Completed] Ice Heart request complete!
48/[Ralph's Request Completed] Lavastein Stone request complete!
49/[Ralph's Request Completed] Zirconia's Egg request complete! …Should I have hatched the egg? Seems like a waste…
50/[Ralph's Request Completed] Lightning Dragon's Horn request complete! Lightning was one tough Dragon…
51/The Pope turned a Palace Warrior into a Dark Warrior…the horror! What is the Pope planning? And who was that person the Pope talked to…?
52/The fisherman I met on South Island said the days when the Deities rules were the golden times. Back then, multiple springs granted blessings on each village. But now, the only spring left is owned by the Pope, so miracles only happen in the capital. The island near the fisherman's home is frequented by storms…I should restore that spring quickly!
53/The Dark Magic Stone is valued incredibly highly in the criminal world, they say. When a Dark Magic Stone was found in Lalaque Forest, a Warrior tried to steal it before the other Warriors could send it to the Pope. But when he touched the stone, he instantly lost his mind! The Dark Magic Stone does have immense magic power…but it's very dangerous to Humans.
54/Balt, the Forest Spirit, always guards the passage to the north. So I have to make a detour each time…I tried chasing it away, but it was just too strong for me. Well…Balt does also keep the Warriors away from my house, so I'm glad!
55/I beat Balt! Now I don't have to make a detour when I travel up! …But now I think the Warriors will show up near my house…
56/This is my first time at a temple, but it feels very familiar…why is that?
57/Luna gave ma an Ice Magic Spellbook…Luna may act distant, but I think she's very lonely. Maybe I'll bring my favorite food next time?
58/Luna's not at her house these days. What happened to her?
59/Oh, my…Luna was captured, too! I want to defeat the Pope and rescue Luna!
60/I defeated Nightmare, even though it was stupendously strong! Even the ancient Deities couldn't hunt it down…does that mean I'm that much stronger? I'm not afraid of anyone who tries to scare me anymore!
61/I met Alfredo again. He's given up on being a Warrior and will take up farming…I think he's grown up now. So, many people yearn for the days of the Deities to come again…?
62/I was safe from harm at the cliff, because Justice held me tight…! It was unexpected, since he hated me so…! Maybe he's not such a bad person after all…? I mean, he is pretty awesome…
63/I didn't know that I leaned on Justice as I slept…it was subtly pleasing…and……………hehe.
64/An ugly, black bird was getting cheeky, so I wanted to teach it a lesson…but it dodged all of my attacks! I think I can catch it if I attack quickly with my boar. I'll return home, then try to catch it later!
