event:0

heroin_normal:Oh…blondie…?

event:1

heroin_normal:Whatcha doin'?

event:2

justice_normal:I told you there would be no mercy next time…

heroin_sigh:So edgy…!

heroin_normal:But you have no sword…? It looks like you're out on a walk…do you really want to fight right now?

heroin_normal:I mean, with the cliff thing and all…

justice_normal:…

event:3

heroin_smile:Thanks for what you did back then.

justice_normal:What?

heroin_shy:You were hurt trying to save me. I remember you holding me…

justice_normal:That's…

heroin_smile:Don’t' just stand there. Sit down…

justice_normal:……

event:4

justice_normal:That's because you saved that child.

justice_normal:I couldn't let someone who helped a Human get hurt.

heroin_smile:You were so amazing! Really!!

justice_normal:Eh……

heroin_shy:Everyone says they'll kill me, but you were the first one to save me!

justice_normal:……

justice_normal:I see. You're always on the wanted list…

justice_normal:But with such powers, you're not afraid of Warriors, are you?

heroin_sigh:I trained myself to survive…I wasn't always this powerful.

heroin_sigh:I've been close to death so many times…and it scares me…! What if a stronger Warrior comes for me…?

justice_normal:Yet you don't seem to be in terror right now. Have I been lax in my training…?

heroin_sigh:No, you're really much stronger than a normal Warrior! It's hard to defeat you…

heroin_smile:But I'm not scared of you anymore!

heroin_smile:You're the first Human to have a chat like this with me…

heroin_shy:The first Human to save me…the first one to hold me…

heroin_shy:You know…I…

justice_normal:Ah…enough…

heroin_smile:Hehe, so what were you doing out here?

justice_normal:……

heroin_normal:(…Oh…his stony face hardened even more…)

heroin_normal:…Never mind. Don't have to tell me!

justice_normal:I was thinking about what the right path is.

heroin_sigh:The right path…? Boring…

justice_normal:After the Demon War, all the Laws given to us by the Demons were discarded.

justice_normal:Now, the Law is defined anew and handed down to us by the Pope, who has been chosen by the spring.

heroin_sigh:*yawn* …

justice_normal:But by chance, I once read the forbidden Book of Law written by the Demons…

justice_normal:And shockingly, their Laws were no different than the Pope's…

heroin:……

justice_normal:Then what was the purpose of our revolution?

justice_normal:I was taught that the goal of the revolution was to throw away the shackles of the Demons and stay on the right path…

event:5

heroin:*snore* …

justice_normal:…?

event:6

justice_normal:Unbelievable…a Witch leaning on a Warrior to sleep…?

heroin:*heavy breaths*

event:7

blackBird_normal:Did you sleep well?

heroin_surprised:Oh…I must have dozed off…

blackBird_normal:He said he didn't bring his blade, but that there would be no mercy next time.

heroin_sigh:…No mercy, sure…heh.

event:8