aramute:Ah, Lucia.

heroin_smile:Hello!

aramute:I knew you would solve everything.

aramute:Of course, I truly apologize for all the pain you had to endure.

aramute:But I also knew that you had the strength to overcome all obstacles.

heroin_sigh:*sigh* …It really was hard for me.

heroin_sigh:Think what would have happened if I failed!

heroin_sigh:The number of times I almost died!

aramute:Haha…yet you did not die, not once.

heroin_sigh:That's too result-focused, I think…

aramute:The flow of the world dances according to our will.

aramute:The War may have temporarily slain our bodies through the hands of the Humans…

aramute:But our will still remained, guiding the Human world unseen.

heroin_surprised:What…? You can do that?

aramute:It seems Elysion has not yet educated you fully on the Pureblood Deities.

aramute:Lucia. You cannot die.

heroin_surprised:?!

aramute:Even in death, only your body withers. Your soul, your will, your power - these do not.

heroin_surprised:Whoa…really?!

aramute:Of course. Did you think Elysion would have abandoned an infant in the forest, if not so?

aramute:You may not have known it, but our blessings were with you always…

aramute:Especially Elysion's.

aramute:It was Elysion who informed Balt each time the Warriors attempted to approach your home.

heroin_surprised:Oh…I didn't…

heroin_sigh:But wait…

heroin_sigh:If I were immortal and could rise again…

heroin_sigh:Why would you need to protect me?

aramute:Ha.

aramute:Simple - Elysion did not wish to see your flesh be pierced by the Warriors' blades.

aramute:Immortal you may be…

aramute:Yet she could not bear to neglect her own daughter.

heroin_sigh:I guess it was kinda pointless for me to struggle to survive, then…

heroin_sigh:Still, I'm scared of my body dying.

heroin_sigh:…It's going to hurt!

aramute:Haha. Yes, it does hurt.

heroin_normal:Anyway, that was a huge shocker for me.

heroin_smile:Hehe! I'm invincible…I mean, immortal…

heroin_sigh:Still, it will hurt when I get hurt, so…I'm going to care for my body, just like I always have!

aramute:That is the nature of things.

aramute:Well, then. I have much work to do…

aramute:I would love to talk more, but I must resume my duty.

heroin_smile:Of course, Lord Aramute!

heroin_smile:Keep up the good work!!

event:0
