event:0

rivia:Uggh…aaah…uggh…

heroin_crisis::*gasp gasp*…

blackBird_normal:Didn't expect her to have absorption powers…

blackBird_normal:Thank goodness she wasn't at the Pope's side.

heroin_crisis:I know…! If she fought at his side, we might have been done for.

rivia:!?

rivia:What do you mean by that? The Pope…no…

heroin_normal:Yes.

heroin_normal:The Pope is dead.

rivia:You lie…!!

heroin_normal:Look. The Pope schemed with Fallen Deities and was planning for a horrible future.

event:1

rivia:Silence!!

rivia:You filthy Witch!!

justice:Livya. Stop.

event:2

rivia:Jus…Justice?

event:3

heroin_smile:Justice! How did you come here?

justice:I've been investigating the traces of the Pope. Such as the hidden places where he stashed the Dark Magic Stone with his lackeys…

justice:This closed mine is one of them.

rivia:……

justice:Livya.

justice:I had heard that you went on a secret mission…yet you were so near.

justice:And you left without saying goodbye.

rivia:Justice…you see…

justice_normal:The Pope is dead.

justice_normal:And the Dark Warriors were the Pope's army to wage a war.

rivia:What…what did you say…?

justice_normal:He was preparing for war, scheming with Crown to sacrifice countless Warriors.

justice_normal:It was all to dethrone the king.

rivia:Is this true…?

blackBird_normal:She barely listened to us, but just accepts Justice's words without question. What?

heroin_sigh:I know…

event:4

justice_normal:And this Deity uncovered the Pope's plan and saved Vavelia Village.

rivia:Oh……

event:5

justice:Livya.

rivia:…Yes…?

justice_normal:You craved power, too?

rivia:…!!

rivia:No…no!

rivia:You know I wouldn't!

justice_normal:Then how do you explain what you've become?

rivia:I…I just wanted…

justice_normal:A shame. I thought you were the only comrade I could trust…

rivia:Justice! Listen to me!

rivia:I…I just wanted to commit myself to the Pope's dream!

justice_normal:The Pope lured Warriors with promised of power, so that they would participate in the dark magic experiments.

justice_normal:Just as he did with you.

rivia:No! That's not it…!

rivia:NO!!

event:6

rivia:*sob sob*… 

justice_normal:…

rivia:That's not it…

rivia:The Pope said we must help the people by utilizing the springs fully…

rivia:He said the Dark Magic Stone experiments were the stepping stones for restoring the springs.

rivia:He also said he required someone without greed for this experiment…

rivia:He said that is was a dangerous experiment, but…with my sacrifice, we may not need to lose more Warriors.

rivia:So I gladly volunteered…

rivia:And…if I hadn't…

rivia:If I hadn't volunteered…

rivia:Then…

rivia:You would have……

heroin_normal:……

event:7

justice_normal:I'm sorry, Livya, but…as you have become a Dark Warrior, I must execute you.

rivia:…Justice!

justice:I am sorry…I'll try to make it painless!

event:8

heroin_normal:Wait, Justice!

event:9

justice:Why should I?

heroin_normal:I couldn't think properly during the fight, but…

heroin_normal:She couldn't be a corrupted Warrior who craved for power.

rivia:…

justice:……

blackBird_normal:The fact that her mind is still alive and well despite absorbing the dark magic is the proof.

blackBird_normal:The Dark Warriors lose their minds, because…

blackBird_normal:The dark magic intensifies their lust for power. And that drives Humans mad.

blackBird_normal:But your friend still has a clear mind.

justice:Oh……

heroin_sigh:Also…

heroin_sigh:She has no magic power left…she will die soon.

justice_normal:…!!

rivia:…

event:10

heroin_normal:Poor thing… she was used by the Pope.

heroin_normal:She seems to be a close friend of yours…

heroin_normal:At least give her a proper goodbye.

rivia:…

justice_normal:Livya…

heroin_normal:I'll excuse myself.

event:11

blackBird_normal:A Human should have been devoured by the power…

blackBird_normal:I think that girl Livya really volunteered for the experiment out of pure loyalty.

blackBird_normal:She had no thirst for power or fame.

blackBird_normal:Whew, that's a new one.

heroin_normal:There's more to that.

blackBird_normal:…?

heroin_normal:She wanted to protect someone.

blackBird_normal:Protect who?

heroin_normal:You're too male to notice.

blackBird_normal:What nonsense is that? I've served you my whole life, and you think I don't know about protecting someone?

heroin_normal:Idiot, you wouldn't know.

blackBird_normal:What are you talking about?

heroin_angry:I told you - too male…

event:12

heroin_normal:Is it over?

justice_normal:I misunderstood her…she was such a pure person…

heroin_normal:You really did.

justice_normal:She was precious…and the only friend I could trust…

heroin_normal:For Livya, it was much more than that.

justice_normal:I know. I wasn't worthy of her.

heroin_sigh:(…Dumb as rocks)

event:13

heroin_shy:Is it…over?

justice_normal:Yes…I misunderstood her. She was so pure and precious…

justice_normal:The Pope used Livya.

heroin_shy:You were really close, huh?

justice:Everyone complained that I only upheld justice and was stubborn.

justice:But not Livya.

justice:In fact, she acknowledged my values and supported me.

justice:And so our friendship grew.

heroin_shy:For Livya… it may have gone deeper than that.

justice:Yes. Friendship knows no bounds.

heroin_shy:Idiot. It could have been more than friendship!

justice:What are you talking about?

heroin_sigh:Never mind…

event:14