rarakWarrior:Good day, Lady Lucia!

heroin_smile:Hi!

heroin_normal:What are you doing here?

rarakWarrior:Well…now that there's no Witch Hunt and it's an age of peace…

rarakWarrior:We really have nothing much to do, haha…

heroin_normal:I think I have nothing much to do, either - ever since you stopped hunting me, hehe.

heroin_normal:So you're just lounging about?

rarakWarrior:Well…we are investigating one unsolved case.

heroin_normal:…?

rarakWarrior:For a while, there have been many disappearances in Lalaque Forest.

rarakWarrior:We used to think the victims were fruit gatherers attacked by wild animals…

rarakWarrior:But the problem is, there are never any bodies to be found.

blackBird_normal:Hmm…

rarakWarrior:We Warriors decided that these were animal attacks…

rarakWarrior:But the village rumors place the blame on a Witch.

heroin_sigh:A Witch…?

rarakWarrior:They're not referring to the former Deities, no.

rarakWarrior:They're talking about an actual Witch of Lalaque Forest, one who devours Humans.

heroin_normal:Whoa…a real Witch…

heroin_normal:But if you found no bodies…then there are no survivors…

heroin_normal:So you don't have any evidence of a Witch, right?

rarakWarrior:Recently, there was one survivor who suffered at the hands of the Witch.

rarakWarrior:He has seen the Witch.

heroin_surprsied:Oh…!

rarakWarrior:But he has a tendency to exaggerate…so he's not very credible.

heroin_sigh:Still, shouldn't you investigate him?

rarakWarrior:That won't be necessary. In fact…

rarakWarrior:He's such a liar that he boasted he knew the lair of the White Witch, back when you were called a Witch.

rarakWarrior:He would say anything to get some attention.

heroin_sigh:Oh…

heroin_sigh:(I think I know who the survivor is…)

rarakWarrior:Anyway, don't mind him. We will take care of this.

rarakWarrior:It won't be proper for a person of your status to be invested in our small village!

event:0
