event:0

vMan-1:Eeeeeek!! What's that?!!

event:1

townPeople:Whoaaaa!!

vMan-1:It came flying from the Pope's Castle!!

oldMan-1:The sky is tainted in darkness…the end is near…

vMan-2:What is the Pope doing…?! A Dragon is loose upon the village…!!

nCrown:Humans…the Pope was devoured by dark magic. He cannot protect you any longer.

nCrown:Despair in the face of absolute power. Despair, and obey!!

event:2

townPeople:Aaaaaack!!!

nCrown:Hahaha…this is too easy! I should have crushed them with force from the beginning…!!!

nCrown:To think I tried to cooperate with the Pope…HAHAHA!!

event:3

temar:……

nCrown:Temar…?

nCrown:You were supposed to guard Durok's temple!

temar:My master commands me to protect this village.

nCrown:…What? Hahahaha!! That is hilarious!!!

nCrown:The Humans were the ones who killed your master and stole his spring!! Don't you know this?

nCrown:I will avenge Durok for you. Move aside.

temar:The Master knew of your plot with the Humans, right from the start.

nCrown:You're speaking nonsense, as did Aramute…they knew it all along, you say?

nCrown:Knew what?! Nothing but words, words of weaklings who were slain by Humans!!

temar:It is for the good of the Humans.

nCrown:More nonsense!!

temar:You know full well that the Humans envied the power of the Deities. You craved that power the most, after all.

nCrown:All beings naturally crave power. What is wrong with that?!

temar:The Humans tried to emulate the power of the Deities…and lost their souls to the Dark Magic Stones in their lust for strength.

nCrown:And the Pope also died in agony in front of his Warriors, devoured by the magic he sought.

nCrown:And he couldn't even control it…such foolishness…Hahaha!

temar:Indeed. And the Warriors witnessed it. And now, the Humans of this village are listening to your words.

temar:This shows them the end of those who seek dark power in vain like the Pope.

nCrown:What?

temar:The Humans only believe what is shown to them. If you only tell them the truth, they want to test it ever more.

temar:So, it was the plan of the Deities to directly show the Humans the error of their ways, and then to restore them. 

nCrown:……Ha?

nCrown:……Hahahaha…HAHAHAHA!!

nCrown:That is their most idiotic plan in 800 years. They killed themselves, just to show something?

temar:……

nCrown:But guess what? They might have succeeded in showing the truth…

nCrown:But they failed to restore anything. You can't defeat me, not when I have completely absorbed the Dark Magic Stones!

event:4

nCrown:Well? You came here to put me down, no? Try using your breath, I dare you!!

temar:If we fight, the village will be destroyed.

nCrown:So…? Then why are you here? As a distraction?

event:5

arua:Ha…so the Daughter of Elysion has finally done it.

event:6

aimhard:The Little Lady has gathered all the magic power already? That is amazing!

event:7

durok:Success.

event:8

aramute:What a mess…I have to work busily just as I wake up?

event:9

nCrown:Let's stop fooling around, shall we?

event:10

allPeople:Aaaaack!!

nCrown:Hehe…it's been a while since I had to control my power…

temar:Uggh…

nCrown:Oh dear…I think about half of the villagers are now dead…what will you do?

nCrown:The village entrance is burning, and the Pope's Castle has collapsed. The Humans can't escape, and are in despair…Hehe.

nCrown:Is this also part of their plan?

temar:Stop…

nCrown:You said they wanted to teach the Humans about the futility of power? Then they would teach it to their descendants…

nCrown:But if they all die, that plan was for nothing, right?

event:11

nCrown:Perish along with the village, Temar!!

event:12

nCrown:…Aaaarrgh……what is this?!!

nCrown:…This is…Aimhard's barrier??

event:13

aimhard:Hello, Jude…you won't be able to break through my barrier!

nCrown:How…how are you still alive…?

nCrown:No matter…I will just break this barrier…!!

durok:My turn.

event:14

nCrown:Gaaah…I won't be stopped like this…so…helplessly…!!

durok:Aimhard. A barrier will one day break if attacked constantly. You must overpower with strength, as I have, in order to attain perfection.

aimhard:What? Do you not know that a barrier has to be in place first for your work to be possible at all?

arua:…Squabbling again, as soon as you two meet each other…

nCrown:Gah…Gaaaaaah!!!!

arua:…How rude…

event:15

nCrown:Grrr…uggh…

arua:Ready to be silent?

arua:Aramute. You should do the honors, no?

aramute:Very well.

nCrown:Lord Aramute…

aramute:Jude. You tempted so many Humans, and now this is your end.

nCrown:With such power…why did you give your lives to the Humans…?

aramute:Do you not see? Look at what ugly creatures the Pope, tainted by darkness, and you have become.

aramute:Yes, it is not just you and the Pope. There were so many who were drunk on dark power…

aramute:But this moment shall be recorded in history, and the Humans will learn of their mistakes.

nCrown:If you knew everything, then why didn't you stop me?!!

nCrown:…I served you for 800 years…yet…was I nothing but a bait to start your plan?!

aramute:I know and recognize the effort you put into serving me for 800 years.

aramute:But I also know well that you were also always ready to bite the hand that fed you, intoxicated by the lust for power.

nCrown:Grrrr……………

aramute:You were never set up as bait.

aramute:You chose to walk that path…

aramute:Thank you for playing your part. Now perish.

event:16

durok:It is done.

aimhard:But the village is in ruins…

aramute:Elysion, it is your time to shine.

eliy:Jude killed too many Humans with brute force.

eliy:I will barely have any magic power left after I revive all the slain Humans, but…I'll do my best!

event:17