man-1:Whew, today's not my day…

woman-2:What are we to do? My family's run out of fruit, so if we can't get them today…

man-2:Same here.

event:0

heroin_normal:What's the matter?

woman-1:Wild dogs have appeared again in Lalaque Village.

event:1

man-3:There's more of them than usual today…We can't drive them off.

woman-1:Maybe we could ask the Warriors for help?

man-2:You think those government lackeys will care about us poor folk?

man-1:Indeed. The Warriors only hunt Witches and monsters. They're not interested in wild dogs.

heroin_normal:(They're here to pick the fruit of that tree…)

event:2

event:3

allPeople:Whoaaa!!

woman-1:Oh dear!!

event:4

heroin_smile:I defeated them! Now you can pick all the fruit you want!

man-1:Wi…Witch!

woman-1:Eeeeek!! A Witch is standing next to me!!

heroin_normal:I was trying to help. Why are you all so shocked?

man-2:Run…run away!! It's the Black Witch!!

allPeople:Waaaaah!! Help!!

event:5

heroin_sigh:*sigh* …Thankless fools!

heroin_normal:…Eh?

event:6

heroin_normal:…Aren't' you going to run away?

woman-2:Spare me. My little sibling are starving, so I have to gather those fruit. I don't know when the wolves will appear again, so…

heroin_sigh:*sigh* …I never said I'd kill you!

woman-2:Then…are you going to let me live?

heroin_normal:I won't kill you! I've never killed a Human, ever!

woman-2:Thank you…! Thank you so much…!!

heroin_sigh:Huh? …Oh…um…hehe…(Never heard anyone thank me…)

woman-2:Thanks to you, my siblings won't have to starve!

heroin_normal:You come here everyday to gather the tree fruit?

woman-2:Yes, but we can only take so much, as there's a limit to how much we can carry.

woman-2:And lowly people like us can't survive without that tree. We have to starve when the wild dogs appear…

heroin_normal:Idiot…eat something else! Don't you have other food?

woman-2:What and fruit are all sent to the castle as taxes, so we have nothing to eat…

heroin_sigh:I see. That's sad…

event:7

allPeople:(Faraway voice) Warriors, come this way!! A girl is still in there…!!
 
event:8

heroin_smile:I'll be going now! Don't forget my mercy!

woman-2:Of course! Tell me your name, Lady Witch…

heroin_smile:It's Pieberry! The Great Witch Pieberry!

sera:Thank you, Lady Pieberry! I'm Sara. I won't forget what you did for me…!!

heroin_smile:Hope you pick lots of fruit!

event:9

heroin_normal:Heh, I don't help Humans…crazy.

event:10