event:0

heroin_normal:The dead Golem is blocking the hillside road.

blackBird_normal:A Golem has no soul, and is already dead. It only moves and attacks due to the evil magic cast on them by Humans.

heroin_sigh:My transport magic has weight limits…and my Return can only target my house…so what do I do?

blackBird_normal:Use the Large Dark Magic Stone to move the Golem.

heroin_normal:The Large Dark Magic Stone? What's that?

blackBird_normal:It's a magic stone created by Humans - they used the smaller stones on themselves.

blackBird_normal:But they were devoured by the dark magic and turned into the Dark Warriors…

blackBird_normal:And so the Deities locked them up in dungeons, but after the War the dungeons collapsed, and some of them are wandering about.

heroin_normal:So I need to defeat the Dark Warriors? Will they be found near the temple?

blackBird_normal:Anyway, they used the Dark Magic Stones on Golem, seeing that it was dangerous to use them on Humans.

blackBird_normal:But the stones were too weak in magic power to fuel Golems, so the Humans fused numerous magic stones together.

blackBird_normal:That became the Large Dark Magic Stone. Only a Dark Golem will yield a rough stone.

heroin_normal:And where is the Dark Golem?

blackBird_normal:I think I saw it in the West Golem Cave.

heroin_normal:The West Golem Cave? Then I'll go look for the Dark Golem!

event:1

blackBird_normal:When you place the Large Dark Magic Stone in its body, it will awaken.

heroin_smile:Okay. Do it!

blackBird_normal:What?

heroin_normal:If I beat it here, it will block the path again. Try to lure it away in that direction.

blackBird_normal:If anything goes wrong, then I'll be killed with a single-

heroin_smile:Don't worry! I'll channel my magic power over there, and then take it down with a single blast!

blackBird_normal:Won't that also blast me, too…?

heroin_normal:So you need to dodge smartly. Go now!

blackBird_normal:*sob*

event:2

heroin_smile:YEAH!! Did you see that? I killed it with a single shot!! I think I'm super-strong now!

blackBird_normal:It's all because I gave you time to channel the magic.

heroin_smile:We should use this tactic for all the strong enemies we meet from now on! Yay!

blackBird_normal:I won't do it. If I didn't dodge quickly, I would have been toast…

heroin_normal:Who are you to say no? You'll do as told!

blackBird_normal:*sob*

event:3