event:0

n:The truth about the Pope and Crown, and their plot have been revealed to the Humans.

n:Justice and his Warriors have come forth as valuable witnesses.

n:The villagers who saw Crown go mad also testified.

n:Mom revived the people killed by Crown with the spring's miracle…

n:And Lord Aramute restored the destroyed Vavelia Village.

n:The collapsed temples were rebuilt, and mom and the other gods were venerated as rulers once again.

n:For Humans still craved for miracles.

n:Now, peace has come to the village.

n:Nothing seems changed.

n:…

n:Not me, of course!

event:1 

heroin:Hehe, I never dreamed of returning here with you, mom!

eliy:Oh, do you remember enjoying the breeze here with mommy?

heroin_smile:No, but I could sense it…it always felt warm when I came here.

eliy:So how did you know we used to come here?

heroin_smile:Because such warmth could only come from you, mom!

heroin_normal:Hey mom, aren't you hungry?

eliy:Oh, you must be hungry!

eliy:Ark!

blackBird_normal:Yes, Master.

eliy:Go fetch us some snacks, please.

blackBird_normal:By the way, Master…when will you dispel this ugly bird magic…?

eliy:Oh, that? I can't…

event:2

blackBird_normal:WHAT?!

eliy:The spell has been in place for so long, it's now become permanent!

heroin_smile:Black Joe! That look suits you well! Right, mom?

eliy:And it will be easier for you to do chores with a smaller body. You used to be too big to fit inside the temple!

heroin_smile:*giggle* We're such a perfect match, mom!

blackBird_normal:That's because you originate from her…literally.

event:3

heroin_smile:Oh, mom! I have someone I want you to meet!

eliy:Someone…?

event:4

justice_normal:…

heroin_smile:You didn't get lost!

justice_normal:Greetings. I'm Justice.

eliy:Ah…the Warrior who was entangled in so many ways with my Lucia, is it?

eliy:How handsome you are!

blackBird_normal:…!!

heroin_sigh:Why did you come in your armor…so stuffy!

justice_normal:You told me to come here right after work…

blackBird_normal:Gaaah! Why are you here?! Begone!!

event:5