heroin:…

blackBird_normal:…

heroin_normal:Whatcha doin'?

blackBird_normal:…I am the Dark Warrior…

heroin:…

heroin_normal:Aren't you Black Joe?

blackBird_normal:I am the Dark Warrior…I am dangerous, so you should run…

heroin_smile:I was looking for a bird, sorry.

heroin_smile:You're the Dark Warrior, you say?

heroin_smile:Let me blast you, since you're so dangerous!

event:0

blackBird_normal:Gaaack.

heroin_sigh:Idiot. What were you trying to pull off?

blackBIrd_sad:Waaah!!

heroin_normal:What is your problem these days?

blackBird_sad:As if you care! You're just going to tell me to get used to it!

heroin_sigh:*sigh* …Fine. I'll listen. What is your problem?

blackBird_sad:I used to be a really cool, powerful bird!! I was an awesome Guardian Beast!!

blackBird_sad:I was the most popular among my kind!

blackBird_sad:Ever since I was cursed with the Ugly Bird spell, all my folks laughed at me!! And they ignored me for my ugliness!

blackBird_sad:I have no more friends, and now my eternal master, a Deity no less, delights in teasing and belittling me!!

blackBird_sad:Waaaaahh!!!

heroin_sigh:…

heroin_sigh:I didn't know you were a loner…why didn't you tell me earlier?

blackBird_sad:*sob sob* Waaah!!!

heroin_sigh:From now on, I'll ignore you slightly less. So stop crying! There!

blackBird_sad:I'm just a worthless slave!! Waaaahh!!

heroin_normal:…

heroin_normal:I apologize. I'm sorry.

blackBird_sad:Oh no, how can I blame you, noble Deity?

blackBird_normal:This is all because of my worthlessness.

event:1

heroin_normal:Black Joe.

blackBird_normal:Oh yes, Great Master? What words do you have for this lowly slave?

heroin_normal:……

heroin_normal:You're my precious friend.

blackBird_normal:…!

event:2

heroin_normal:Mom told me. You played with me a lot when I was little, right?

blackBird_normal:……

heroin_normal:I remember some of it. You were by my side when mom was busy, and I did some really stupid things.

blackBird_normal:…

heroin_normal:You were with me even after the war, right?

heroin_normal:I vaguely remember a black ball-thing always bringing me food.

heroin_normal:And you left when I could wield magic on my own…

blackBird_normal:…

heroin_normal:But still looked out for any Warriors who might come near my house.

heroin_normal:I played dumb, but I knew about it all.

heroin_normal:Don’t call yourself a slave. I think of you as a friend, so if you don't…

heroin_normal:Then my heart will break.

blackBird_sad:I…I didn't know…

blackBird_sad:…*sob* …Master…

blackBird_sad:*sniffle* …

blackBird:Waaaaahh!!! Master!!!

heroin_smile:Now do you believe me?

blackBird_sad:You are my one and only master, Lady Lucia! All my friends abandoned me for my looks…!!

blackBird_sad:Yet you call me your friend…I am so touched!!

heroin_smile:Yes! We're friends!

heroin_smile:We're like siblings! That's why we squabble and fight all the time!

blackBird_normal:Indeed!

blackBird_normal:I was so wrong! Hahaha!!

blackBirD_normal:I am sorry for making you upset!

heroin_smile:Is my Black Joe back?

blackBird_normal:Of course! I had been so stupid!

heroin_smile:*giggle*

blackBird_normal:Kehehe!!

event:3

heroin_normal:Now that you've regained your senses, it's time for the pain.

blackBird_normal:Huh?

event:4

heroin_normal:You better not run away ever again!

blackBird_sad:Urrk…I thought we were precious friends…

heroin_normal:Like siblings! This is our 'blazing hot' expression of friendship.

blackBird_normal:Gah…thank you…?

event:5