heroin_sigh:*sigh* …You again?

alfredo_normal:…

heroin_sigh:You now know the location of my house…you leave me no choice…

event:0

alfredo_normal:!! Wait, WAIT!!

heroin_sigh:What? Any last words? I'll hear them, if you want…

alfredo_normal:I didn't come here to fight! I came to say thank you!

heroin_normal:What?

alfredo_normal:I used to chase you, so that I could prove my worth. Hunting down a Witch would make me a hero, I thought!

heroin_sigh:So?

alfredo_normal:But you told me to "hold on what I already have", right?

alfredo_normal:I was obsessed with you, to become the best Warrior…but I had forgotten what truly mattered.

heroin_sigh:You were a bit obsessive, but that's okay. You always had ample gold…

alfredo_normal:Don't interrupt me!

heroin_normal:So what was the thing that truly mattered to you?

alfredo_normal:My mother.

alfredo_normal:I chose to become a Warrior to gain honor for my mother…

alfredo_normal:But along the way, I forgot about her and only obsessed over chasing you.

alfredo_normal:So I decided to quit being a Warrior and take up farming.

heroin_smile:Excellent choice. You really sucked at swordplay!

alfredo_normal:…

alfredo_normal:Thank you, White Witch. I came here to tell you that.

heroin_sigh:Well, that's not the problem.

alfredo_normal:?

heroin_sigh:You found out where I live…I can't let you go.

alfredo_normal:Hey, now…I knew about your house long ago!

alfredo_normal:And I never told anyone…so that I'd be the one to capture you!!

heroin_normal:Can I trust your words?

alfredo_normal:Else, why would I have come alone?!

heroin_smile:Just kidding. I already knew.

alfredo_normal:…

heroin_normal:I got what you said, so go now. I have to go hunting!

event:1

alfredo_normal:Be strong, White Witch. You're not alone…

event:2

heroin_normal:What did you say?

alfredo_normal:Many people miss the days of the Deities - my mother included. Most are poor folks like us.

alfredo_normal:I don’t' know when it will be, but I'll wait for your time to shine.

event:3
