0/Ha, got something!
1/It's a small one! Found game!
2/Hiyaah!
3/Yes! Got it!
4/I lost it! My magic power must not be enough…
5/…Never mind. I don't want to waste my stamina.
6/Ooh! Needed just a bit more…
7/How can I lose that…? That one's sure lucky!
8/Is this gold left by a Warrior? Yay!
9/Heh! It's a pesky Warrior!
10/Let's fight!
11/Aaaaack!
12/Whew…just a weakling. With not much money, even…
13/Hiyaaaah!!
14/Ayah!
15/Gah…too much… Gotta run!
16/Run! Run away!
17/It's evening already? I should fuse all the gathered ingredients!
18/Let's see…I think I can fuse a 3-Flame Central Magic Circle!
19/Yay! I fused a new magic!
20/Running complete! I think I worked out hard today, too! I'll sleep soundly!
21/To the bed…my fluffy bed!
22/Yes! Now I can craft something! To home!
23/To home! Zoom!
24/Finally, a new offense magic is fused! I should put it in a slot!
25/Grrrrr…grr…
26/Ah…did I overexert my self while out? …I'm so tired!
27/Hehe! Now I'll force all the Warriors who cross me to kneel and worship me!
28/I can't combine magic circles yet - I haven't fused any magic circles.
29/Perhaps I should call it a day? Better not skip training before going to bed!
30/*sigh* …I need to rest before I train…
31/Let's run!
32/Done running! Running sure felt good!
33/*yawn* I really slept well!
34/A Warrior? How did he come to this forest?
35/This is…Mind Control magic? So that's what he had, despite not being able to cast magic.
36/Facing a Warrior is exhausting…I should head home quickly!
37/Hmm…it would be nice to ride it, right? I should cast Mind Control with my last attack!
38/*sigh* …My HP is low…gotta rest.
39/*sigh* …I don't have much HP…this is too hard.
40/Huh?! A swamp! It's too yucky to approach!
41/There's a town across the bridge. I was almost hunted down by Warriors the last time I crossed it…
42/I see a small island over there…something's shining brightly, too…I want to go there!
43/Woohoo!
44/Hahaha! What an ugly bird!
45/I'm in the mood for some bird meat.
46/Keke, I'll roast it and eat it!
47/Ooh!! Run, run!
48/That was a close one…
49/Eeeek!!
50/Ooh…ugh…
51/That stupid bird!! You'll be sorry next time!!
52/Wait…this seems like that island, right? I must have drifted here by chance…
53/*grunt grunt*
54/Whoa…a huge lion!!
55/…I care not.
56/Right? I'm probably not very tasty. I'll be going, then!
57/I care not for a husk…I shall destroy you if you are not the true one!
58/Hey…hey!
59/ROAR!
60/*gasp gasp* …I won!!
61/It seemed like an extraordinary beast, being able to talk and all.
62/It was a Guardian Beast of the Deities. Master, I believe a Deity Temple is ahead of us.
63/Deities? What are those?
64/Gods who once ruled over Humans. They've all been eliminated by Humans now.
65/So it was protecting the temple, despite its master being long gone…that's kind of sad.
66/Even so, its dead master cannot return. It's better to move on with one's life.
67/Whatever. I want to see what the temple looks like! Let's go inside.
68/Chop-chop-cop
69/Hot!!
70/Hey, rabbit…Have you seen a bird that looks like q(%◇ %)p?
71/I do not acknowledge you, husk.
72/What…? But I just defeated it!
73/A Guardian Beast can't be brought down so easily. And it will recover quickly especially if near the spring near a temple!
74/You tell me that now?!
75/Grr…
76/Too narrow…
77/Wow! Looks tasty!
78/You are a brave witch.
79/To honor your courage, I shall…willingly give you a pound of my flesh.
80/Huh? A pound is nothing - I'll eat all of you! You'll last me a month, probably!
81/Look…look here! Little Witch, my flesh will regrow with time…! So it will be best if you let me live.
82/Oh…well, fine, then!
83/I'm back! Give me some pudding!
84/How rude, Little Witch. I am the King of Puddings.
85/Ha?!
86/Spare me…as you know…
87/I know. Just give me the pudding.
88/Hehe!
89/Yeah! A huge helping of strawberry pudding!!
90/Oww…what is my honey doing, when I'm being harassed like this?!
91/Yuck! A dark one…can't eat that.
92/Kiyeeeh!
93/*sigh* …That was a messy one.
94/I don't think the ingredient I'm looking for exists beyond this place.
95/Give me your gold!
96/Keke, this is my turf. Give me 50,000 gold for entry.
97/Oww…! But I'm the boss of this cave…!
98/Shut up! Just follow me quietly!
99/…
100/This one has a Magic Slab!
101/Who are you calling ugly, pig-face?!
102/Wow! A talking bird? This is better than a parrot! Hey you…be my pet!
103/Shut it. Don't interrupt me when I'm eating!
104/What the…? Why you…!
105/Help…spare me! I'll serve you forever as my master!!
106/Hehe, that's what I wanted to hear! Say "My beautiful master" three times.
107/What?
108/Did I hear you just talk back at me? You…!
109/My beautiful master! My beautiful master! My beautiful master!
110/…Hehe!! That felt good! You're my minion from now on!
111/It's an honor!
112/It got away…! It's too fast…maybe I can catch it by using the boar during battle…!
113/Oh! We meet again! I'll catch you this time!
114/Kekeke, you're too slow to catch me.
115/Witch…! The White Witch!!
116/Everyone calls me the Black Witch. You're weird.
117/Your hair is white. Anyway! I'll defeat you and prove that I'm a Warrior!
118/…!
119/Hiya! Long time no see! You're resting here, as usual?
120/Always so bright, Black Witch.
121/Well, you're the only Human I can meet safely, and you're also my supplier! How long will you be staying this time?
122/As always - 48 hours in this area, then I shall pass again in about 3 days.
123/Okay! By the way, how about a discount for your frequent customer?
124/Your smile will not work. Remember, I am also risking my life trading with you…
125/Pffft…so dramatic!
126/Do you have anything worthwhile?
127/My goods are always top-notch.
128/I haven't gathered the ingredients I need.
129/Our will shall guide them, and they shall seek us out once more. - March 5th, 600, Aruav
130/Huh? There's something underneath the diary!
131/Wow…an S-class Pudding. Impressive, Black Witch. This is why I relish trading with you!
132/There is a Pudding Contest afoot. If I present the King Pudding there, the chefs will sell the souls to me! So I will reward you handsomely if you bring me one.
133/I value you more than the Warriors, Witch. You always keep your end of the bargain.
134/Psssht! Haaa! Phew!
135/Weee! So relaxing!
136/Oww…I like getting stronger…but my hands hurt…
137/My head is clear!
138/*yawn*
139/Hehe, I think I practiced really well!
140/I'm suck of running away from Warriors!
141/My days of running away are over! Today I fuse my Flame Magic!
142/After I fuse my Flame Magic, I'll burn them all!! No more running away!
143/I've gathered the core ingredients, so let's head out to collect the final minor ingredients.
144/I just need 2 Superdry Leaves and Blue Sand…they're nearby, so this will be over in a jiffy!
145/I've fused my offense magic, so it's time to warm up in the Pudding Cave!
146/Eh? You're that pathetic Warrior! What are you doing here?
147/Haha…I saw you fly over to this island! Coming here was worth risking my life!!
148/You…drifted here, didn't you?
149/……Yes. But that's not important!
150/And you got lost while looking for me, right?
151/……Yes. For hours, actually…
152/…Do you happen to know the way out? Help me, please.
153/Of course I do! But I'm not going to tell you! Pffft!!
154/Bah! Then I'll defeat you and make you talk!
155/Idiot…you're weak!
156/There is Golem with a Magic Slab in the Golem Cave behind your house…? And you can acquire it quickly?
157/Incredible! I can finally meet the quota! Thank you, Black Witch!
158/I shall be going, then. I hope to trade with you again…beware the Warriors.
159/The Bigcrab does not appear in exposed coastlines any longer. They may live in isolated islands, perhaps. The Bigcrabs have hard shells and strong pincers, so be careful.
160/Oww…hunting Bigcrab is hard!
161/Haha. You have grown stronger for it. I shall reward you!
162/*gasp gasp* …I…I'm lost!
163/Idiot. Have you been following me?
164/…!!
165/No…no. I was training. Training!
166/Seems like you were hiding here after being chased by the Pudding Queen.
167/Why you…! Let's fight! I'll show you how I've grown in power!
168/You poor, pathetic Warrior. I already defeated the Pudding Queen, so you can just go back the way you came.
169/Squee! Squee! SQUEEEE!(This is my turf. Get lost!)
170/*sigh* …You again?
171/I'll never give up, White Witch!
172/Are you planning to constantly donate gold to me? Try harder.
173/What…huh? A Warrior?!
174/…I've come to the right place, it seems.
175/(This one looks pretty strong…!)
176/Hiyaaaah!
177/Gah…!!
178/Eeek…I don't want to go down there…it's too dark!
179/Black Joe said…that I was abandoned.
180/Maybe I can meet my parents…if I go to the village?
181/…Master? Are you planning to cross the bridge? You know the village lies on the other side, right?
182/The Black Witch…? So it was true that a Witch has appeared in Lalaque Village. It was fortunate that I was dispatched here.
183/Eeek…!! Not again!
184/I told you to kill him the last time! You fool!
185/Fool? You're SO dead…later!
186/I won't lose like last time, so you better be ready for me!
187/*sigh* …We never should have come to this village…
188/You come seeking your death…so here I come!
189/Spare me!! Spare me!!
190/Gwwwwrrr Kwaaah!
191/Ha! That was nothing!
192/*gasp gasp* …
193/That was dangerous! Why would you want to come to this village?!
194/Why do you care?! If I die, you'll be free!
195/Master…!
196/You hate me, right?! Everyone hates me. The Warriors…the villagers…everyone!!
197/…Not everyone.
198/My own parents abandoned me! So who wouldn't hate me?
199/…
200/There's an opening on the ceiling inside the Golem Cave. Let's rest and head there.
201/Why?
202/It's the way to Elysion Temple. What you seek lies there.
203/…!
204/You're being suspicious. You know too much. But you look so dumb…
205/…I know stuff, too! I like traveling here and there…!
206/No, that's not what I'm suspicious of.
207/…?
208/Each time we entered a temple, you tired to stop me - and you always knew something.
209/But now, you want to take me to a temple?
210/It's because you've been so gloomy recently. Maybe finding a spring there will cheer you up…
211/……
212/Fine. I won't press it further. Maybe I'm too sensitive right now.
213/You should rest for now! Then we can head to the Golem Cave in the back hill.
214/Ughh…he's so creepy…radiating weird magic power like that…
215/Be careful…it's evil magic power…!
216/It's been awhile since I came here…never thought I'd be back…
217/Whoa!
218/Warrior…!
219/I hear loud noises from there! Warriors, hurry…!!
220/*sigh* This is getting tiresome…
221/That one's strong, so use me. I can boost your DEF by half of your MAG!
222/Brrrrk!
223/Careful. We're near the village, so the more battles we have, the more Warriors will come for us!
224/If I use you, my DEF increases by half of my MAG? Wow…!
225/Oh, right! I have to write my diary before I go to sleep!
226/Diary finished! Now it's time for bed!
227/The Mind Control magic you just gained is not easily fused.
228/To be exact, it's a high-level magic that weakens another's mind to charm it…
229/I don’t know how he got it, but I don't care! Let's put it in a slot!
230/The first slot should be used for offense magic, so maybe I'll put it in the second slot?
231/Equipped! This isn't a Greater Mind Control, so it won't work on Humans…
232/But it will work on beasts…so…I'll delay going to the Pudding Cave for now!
233/A boar has been roaming near my house, so I should catch it by hitting it last with the Mind Control magic!
234/I think it's been damaged enough! Shall I finish it with my Mind Control magic?
235/If I can handle him well, I can ride him to travel quickly.
236/Oh, and cross the swamp, too!
237/He was too quick for me last time. I'll need to be as quick as him this time…!
238/I should try crossing the swamp below. It used to be too filthy for me to cross…
239/I should dispel it when I gain more magic.
240/Grrrrr!!
241/*sigh* …This was really hard. You better pay up!
242/Haha, have I ever disappointed you? A fine trade, indeed!
243/Lavastone can be obtained from Lava the Large Golem. Perhaps it lies deep within the Golem Cave.
244/Grrrrr…Grrrrr…
245/Huh? It's…nicer than I expected?
246/I think it's because of Aslan's smell on you, Master.
247/Really? …Then I'll pluck some of its hair! I think I can use it as a magic ingredient!
248/Lion, I'll borrow some of your hair!
249/Hmm…this way leads to the Pope's Castle…the Castle Warriors are much stronger than the village ones, so I shouldn't go there.
250/Haaaaah!
251/This way leads to the Pudding Cave…the boar won't be there.
252/This way leads to the Golem Cave…the boar won't be there.
253/I remember seeing a boar near my house…
254/I was always curious about the swamp below. I should head there first.
255/The Pudding Cave is to the east…I should test my offense magic there!
256/The ceiling is broken here! The light shines through…
257/Hiyaaah!
258/Equipped!
259/Gah…!! Up so soon?!
260/Go, go, go!
261/Arrgh!
262/Come here!
263/*sigh* …You really aren't very trustworthy.
264/Same species, but I'm not from this area…I'm a stranger here, too…
265/Are you sure the temple is nearby?
266/Very, very sure. Come on.
267/The entrance has been collapsed. We should look for another way in.
268/This way leads to the Pope's Castle. The Humans invaded the temple from through path.
269/*gasp gasp* …
270/Hiyaaaah!!
271/Eeeek!
272/Gaaah!!
273/Whoa…what is that? …It looks super strong!!
274/But it is slow, so you'll have plenty of chance to attack! You can do it!
275/*gasp gasp* …Finally, I got the Big Dark Magic Stone…!
276/You've come so far! Even the Humans gave up on defeating it…
277/Hehe! Now, let's go to that Golem who was blocking the way!
278/Yiaaah!
279/Gaaah!
280/Arrgh!!
281/Ooh! It's too cold here…!!
282/Yay…My mom's robe is so warm, I don't feel the cold!
283/Here I come!
284/Impressive…that will be all the training for today! Come back when you're ready!
285/*gasp gasp* …Thanks!
286/Hiyaah!!
287/Going up won't be easy…
288/Huh? What is a Warrior doing here…?
289/Warriors are dispatched here, as this is the closest temple from the Pope's Castle.
290/Is this Justice's doing…?
291/Perhaps. Justice is the only Human who witnessed you in the temple.
292/Haaaargh!!
293/Oh…what should I do…?
294/(I see a guard over there…I should find the staff and Black Joe first.)
295/Gaaah!
296/Jude will go mad soon! We must find Lord Aramute's room quickly!
297/Below is the prison! I didn't see Aramute's room here.
298/This leads to the exit! We have to go the other way!
299/I think this is the way, but it's locked!
300/So what if it's locked? We should bash it down!
301/Black Joe…? Did the seal break again when I fainted?!
302/Why is your face so weird…?
303/Grrrrr………
304/…!!
305/Found it! My staff!
306/Oh…I can make out a Teleport Mark here. I can connect the temple with my home!
307/Black Joe!!
308/I can make out a Teleport Mark here…! But I don't know how to use it…
309/(Strange, I can sense Black Joe's energy strongly here. He must be in a prison somewhere!)
310/(Perhaps I should give Luna my favorite food?)
311/Grrrrr…
312/Graargh!
313/Woooo…!
314/Gaaah…!
315/Meow!
316/I am glad I know the Witch. I can get my hands on exotic items!
317/The Black Lion lives on the plain of the northern Lions.
318/I have it!
319/Ha, I can upgrade 10 blades with this…
320/10…blades…?! Give it back! I don't want to endanger myself!
321/Hush. Just take the gold.
322/The Warriors who have swallowed the Dark Magic Stone and is dominated by its power are called the Dark Warriors. They may live deep within the cave.
323/Incredible…you have brought back the Dark Magic Stone!
324/Astounding, Black Witch! You are amazing!
325/The Ice Heart can be obtained from the Old Yetiman of the North Icy Field.
326/You have the Ice Heart. A clean, professional bargain.
327/Get me the Lavastein Stone.
328/Oh…the burning stone…This is my first time seeing the Lavastein Stone with my own eyes. How to carry it, I wonder…
329/Bring me the Zirconia Dragon's Egg. I shall await with hope.
330/Oh, my…!! I honestly did not think you would return with your life…10,000 gold is definitely worth this!
331/Get me Lightning Dragon's Horn. I do not even know if it exists, as it is a legendary Dragon…
332/My word…I cannot believe my own eyes…it actually exists?!
333/You are legendary, Black Witch!!
334/Kyaaah!!
335/Huh…? It's that ugly bird again!
336/I bullied it alto when I was in my true form. I used to call it Pig-hair.
337/Oh…So when you called it Pig0hair before, it recognized you and ran away?
338/I doubted it, but it did recognize me…heh.
339/It's a bit too difficult for me to face right now, so we should make a detour.
340/Yay! Now I won't have to go around anymore!
341/That tree over there had lots of fallen leaves, I think!
342/And this tree had lots of Superdry Leaves, too…
343/And lastly, the Blue Sand is abundant in the sandy beach!
344/Pudding Cave is to the east! The Puddings are weak and tasty - perfect for hunting!
345/*sigh* …With Balt gone, the Warriors are here…!
346/Worshippers…? I better not go down there.
347/West: Pope's Castle(Vavelia Village), East: Lalaque Village
348/South: Lalaque Tree, East: Lalaque Village
349/North: Lalaque Forest North Hill, South: Lalaque Forest South#nEast: Lalaque Village, West: Lalaque Forest West
350/Lalaque Village Entrance
351/North: Aimhard Temple#nEast: Lalaque Forest, Lalaque Village#nWest: Pope's Castle, North Icy Field
352/North: North Icy Field#nWest: Vavelia Village, East: Lalaque Village
353/3On Spirits#nBlast is the Fire Spirit born of fire energy, Balt is the Forest Spirit imbued with the energy of life, and Aeris the Ice Spirit has a hardy soul. Though they cannot speak, each has a mind and intellect. These three may also form as one, and will grant new power to the one who unites them. #n- From the Magic Index of Aramute, the First Temple Lord -
354/What are you good for, I wonder?
355/I know, right? Since I'm pretty useless, don't try to make me do anything.
356/Huh? That coast…
357/Lalaque Village is closest…Does that mean I was born in that village?
358/If we meet…will I be welcomed…?
359/Oh…it's so bright…! The sunlight must be strong up there!
360/Luna!!
361/Oh…?
362/No one is here? Out hunting?
363/Why did you come again?
364/Hehe…I was bored, so I called! I'll come back later!
365/Whatever…I won't stop you, but I'm not saying you should!
366/(I should come back later. When she's bored…?)
367/Oww…I want to go out!
368/Hold on! I'll save you!
369/(Luna's in prison right now…I have to rescue her!)
370/Arrgh!!!
371/No Tresspassing#nNightmare Sealed Area
372/Black Joie said…I was abandoned…
373/So my parents are in the village?
374/The nearest village is Lalaque Village…Will I meet my parents if I go there?
375/……
376/I don't know…I just want to sleep…
377/Ughh…
378/…War…?
379/…And a large bird…
380/…I don't like this…
381/I'll rest at home for a while and then catch that cheeky bird! I'll use the boar to do that!
382/Hey! Let's go to that coast!
383/I heard that Luna now lives in Vavelia Village with her mother.
384/Oh, who might this be? Lady Lucia, the daughter of the noble Elysion!
385/You're embarrassing me…just act normal!
386/Oh, but how can I? You're Lady Lucia! And what might the great lady wish of this humble merchant…?
387/Stop it.
388/Ha, I knew that would unsettle you.
389/It looks thirsty. You said it only drinks clean water?
390/Chirp!
391/I'll play with you after work! Please be patient, my daughter!
392/Here I come!
393/Oh…it's Lady Lucia! You've graced Lalaque Village with your presence…!
394/A Deity! A Deity!
395/Lady Lucia…? I am honored to meet you!
396/I used to flee in terror, calling you the Black Witch…Haha, how rude I was to such a holy Deity…!
397/Oh! What brings you here, Lady Lucia?
398/How amazing! Such large ears!
399/Hello, Deity!
400/Hello, Lady Lucia! We're rooting for you!
401/Greetings, Lady Lucia!
402/Thanks to you, we have nothing to do…haha!
403/Don't mind the one who says he saw the White Witch. His tales about the Witch is probably just hot air.
404/The village is always peaceful. I have nothing much to do.
405/A young Deity. Have you come to see Lord Aramute?
406/Oh, a Deity? A pureblood…or a hybrid…?
407/A new Deity, I see.
408/When the Black Dragon went berserk, I fainted with dread. So terrifying…
409/Lord Aramute did not abandon us. He saved us in our time of need…
410/The prison is under construction. You cannot enter.
411/I have to find Black Joe…I think he went downwards.
412/North: Vavelia Village, Aramute Temple#nSouth: Elysion Temple
413/Have I wandered around too much? I feel so tired! I should sleep more…
